No, I think I think I have it. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Okay. So you guys, yeah, yeah,
you guys are hopping on mid itinerary
today.
I was hoping I would go through the
purpose of our platform because we don't,
we haven't really spent time on that.
And that goes a little bit into the
organization of our features,
which is why Graham is here.
As we did the 10 minute version was super
high level, I don't think.
I think we needed to get a little bit
deeper than that. But I think, Graham,
you're going to jump out at 10 to 11,
so we can catch up on anything you missed
afterwards. That's fine.
Kenny is also here because she has more
knowledge than me on some of these
details.
So we're going to go through that.
But just as a recap for Ali,
because we are mid-curriculum,
So we talked about,
we talked about firm segments in the
first session.
We talked about based on firm segments,
how do we actually set them up in the
book of record?
And so we talked about the firm hierarchy
in the second session.
So you understand when we throw things up
like R codes, secured zone, compass.
OSS slash ISM slash Kyndryl slash book of
record, it's all the same thing. Okay.
I understand kind of the broker code set
up, right?
And the R ranges that fall or the account
ranges that fall within the broker codes.
You understand that we impose a firm
hierarchy on top of that because we have
shared broker codes for firms.
Yeah. Right.
And then so you know that in Firm 360 is
where the firm can refiguration
ultimately originates from starting with
the firm hierarchy,
which includes not just the firm unique
identifier itself,
all the R ranges that we assigned to the
firm,
the broker code that we assigned to the
firm.
The branch code that we sent to the firm,
it also includes the firm hierarchy in
the sense of the parent-child
relationships,
but it does not today include
sub-advisory,
which we'll get into when we in a couple
of weeks time when we go into the
advanced curriculum.
And currently it does not include
anything that a firm has subscribed to
yet,
because that is also a topic of
conversation about how this firm 360 work
with Compass in the future. Today,
it's neither here nor there.
If you want to look at all the things
that a firm has,
like I'm going to use the word subscribe
to because it's an industry term, right?
Do they have certain aspects of Compass?
Do they have add-ons in Compass?
Do they have off-compass stuff?
There's nowhere to see that.
The goal is to get it all into Firm 360
at some point.
And then for Compass to implement what is
assigned to that firm at some point.
But that's a conversation you guys are
going to have with it. OK.
So that's firm 360,
that's a firm hierarchy,
that's the kind of permissioning,
like the base permissioning of what a
firm has access to and any user has
access to.
Do you have any questions before we kind
of move on to how does the platform
handle all of this? No, I'm good. Okay.
Well, sorry, we then also said, well...
I forgot. So we had a discussion,
Ali and I,
also about how things get into the book
of record,
which is really driven by kind of our
custodian caring broker services, right?
So we got, we got the four key,
like I say it four,
I feel like if you ask each and four
individually,
they will say it's three or four and
there are different fours. So my four is.
account opening, account management,
account servicing, right?
So account servicing, order management,
and trade administration,
which includes security administration.
So our four core service areas we have,
you know,
is really makes up our core digital suite,
what we call like everybody needs this.
kind of set of services and that has a
direct interaction of the book of record
because obviously that's the role of the
custodian hearing broker is to facilitate
all of these core interactions, right?
Yeah. Okay, so we understand all of that.
We also got into, well,
our digital strategy is not just about
providing core services.
Right,
it's actually about creating a digital
ecosystem.
where we can actually upsell technology
and create stickiness for their clients
and also create new revenue opportunities
for clients. And so in addition to core,
we also have non-core stuff.
Right? So core versus non-core.
So in the core, everybody gets,
and we're going to dive into the
structure of the core. But for add-ons,
really the role here is, well,
MBN doesn't really build technology.
It's not a core business.
We partner with providers, third parties,
other, you know, even bank apps,
I'm going to call them third parties,
to find ways to generate revenue and
provide value-add services to our firms.
And so whilst the platform actually,
historically, if you look at Old Compass,
kind of mostly manages the core services
with some stuff sprinkled on top,
our new platform has to be flexible to
manage both of these suites of products.
So we're here to develop an ecosystem,
and that's a conversation we're going to
have today.
Yeah, right. So, that's your backdrop,
Ali, in terms of recap, and then context,
and Candi and Kevin,
who decides to listen to the recording.
That's where we started from. OK,
so do we have any questions?
Do you have any questions before we start?
No, we just, I think...
We just talked about, for example,
the feature registration,
feature management,
which was another aspect of our
conversation,
which we were supposed to dig in more,
double click more.
I think it's not the context of this
meeting, but yeah,
I think we talked about that as well.
And no, not so far so good. Yeah.
All right.
So we're going to dive in and then,
because I have an audience,
you guys maybe can help me answer
questions as they come up.
OK, so.
Many years ago,
when we decided to build this new
platform,
we said we're going to be a little bit
different because the purpose of the
platform has changed over the years.
I think, you know,
if you look at Legacy Compass,
it used to be, you know,
it's really just a consolidation point
for stuff we have.
And so you can provide online access for
clients to get to that stuff.
And that stuff was pretty organic.
It was whatever we had.
That was the story there.
And then whatever we didn't have,
we add on top.
And so we actually ended up with a
collection of stuff that you access in
different ways. And we said, well,
that's not really that viable,
because number one,
it's actually created a pretty confusing
environment.
for our clients between the old legacy
secured zone and net rep and OSS and
whatever other tools we have,
you're not really clear at any given
point what you can actually provide for
the firm and what the firm has, right?
So that was a little bit confusing as
well.
If you try to add more capabilities on
top.
of legacy compass,
it actually doesn't scale.
It's a giant monolith.
I think like 1 1/2 person in this floor
knows how to do it properly,
especially on the IT side.
And you guys can attest to that.
Change was hard, change was hard.
And the security model,
I think you saw some of the legacy,
it was very confusing, right?
It mixed data permissions with feature
permissions.
There were some stuff that were hidden
that's not.
very visible,
like the firm configuration required
specialized knowledge.
And adding stuff to it also required
specialized knowledge. And in cases,
I'm not sure if we even have like clear
limitations.
I'm not sure if we understand all the
limitations to it. So that had to change.
On top of that,
we know that our new kind of strategy,
like, I don't know,
you saw the digital strategy page. Yes.
Right? Was was that, you know,
how do we how do we generate recurring
revenue from technology?
How do we at the same time,
obviously not making money for money sake,
but help our firms with their technology
needs?
We needed a platform that scales much
better, right?
So we said new platform should really
have two jobs. Well, one core job,
which is
We want this to be the single digital
entry point for all clients,
for all digital products.
So it's never confusing what you have.
It's actually all encompass,
including things that are not encompassed
today, like a Kris or a digit,
which you access from elsewhere.
It becomes, you know,
very clear from a tracking perspective.
It's clear from a unified access
perspective.
We don't have multiple logins and we can
actually track subscriptions.
and billing very clearly from that
platform.
But it also does 2 sub-functions because
we have this concept of the core that
everybody gets,
and then we also have this concept of an
add-on.
The way our firms interact with core has
a very different pattern.
It's a much more nuanced pattern than
anything that we built on top.
So the platform also has to facilitate.
two models. I need, you know, pretty good,
decent flexibility and configurability of
core services.
And I'll get into why in a second.
It's all about the why for us, right?
And then I need a maybe a speedy agile
model to get to develop that app
marketplace or the app ecosystem that we
talked about.
And then the platform needs to be handled
both, right?
So it's like optimization versus
flexibility. It needs to do both jobs.
Yeah, makes sense. Right.
So how we do that and then maybe before
we get into the how,
maybe just a quick overview.
I did try to hack this page.
It's not done because we never documented
this before. So if you have any questions.
ask and then maybe I'll clarify in the
documentation because I threw this
together before I sent it to you
yesterday.
But just and I use I reused a lot of our
old stuff so it might need tweaking.
So I mean before getting into that we
said well if we're going to have a single
digital entry point.
for all the things that people have
access to,
then a platform needs to do a few
fundamental jobs, right? Of course,
you're in this space.
We talk about platform security.
Obviously,
we need to implement controls around what
a firm has and what a user has.
I think you're very familiar with that
now that you're...
kind of 2 1/2 weeks in.
And it also needs to have configurability
of those things for our users and firms,
right? So at minimum,
it needs to have that.
But once you get into the platform, well,
you need a platform experience.
We call that the container.
You'll hear kind of Ray or Pat,
they always talk about the container,
which is the rest of the platform once
you're in.
how do you host the apps?
It's the app hosting part of it.
To host the apps, you need a few things,
right?
You need to actually be able to kind of
look, you know,
on the feature management side of it,
you need to be able to onboard features
and package them appropriately.
I won't get into this. Again,
this was aspirational.
It was a part of some other crazy
discussion.
So some of these things might not exist,
but I kind of relate the app building or
the app composition part of it,
not too dissimilar to, you know,
like when you go, when you,
if you ran iOS and you built the Apple
Store, right?
You have a toolkit where people can come
and onboard their apps onto your platform.
It's the same idea, but.
Apple spends like billions of dollars on
it. We spend very little money on it.
It's a different problem.
The problem is at a totally different
scale, but the principle is the same.
We need a way to host apps, right,
which means we need the ability to kind
of onboard and bundle and display, right,
and allow users to navigate through any
apps that we onboard.
So we call that the app.
I call it the app platform.
I don't think anybody else does.
Owen calls it that too.
That's about it.
We also need some platform services that
these apps can talk to. So ultimately,
it doesn't matter which app you're using.
You have a, you know,
have a harmonized experience.
So basic things like having task
management, having notifications,
having a global preference management
that can apply to any app in the platform.
We need those services, right? Otherwise,
every single app does their own
notification. You get 15,
000 emails like you actually do today
from us.
You should talk to Devindra about the
number of emails that people get in a
week. It's horrendous.
And it's inconsistent.
Sometimes you're not even sure is this
coming from NBIN or not.
So we have some of those issues.
like document management,
content management, you know,
all this stuff makes a common set of
services that any app can come into and
interact with. And then you can,
the platform itself can present the user
back with something that's more
consolidated,
where it needs the consolidation.
Not everything needs to be brought
together,
but something basic like alerts and
notifications.
Absolutely, right?
You want to see that across the entire
app suite,
so those services should be available.
We're very early days in developing this.
There's some notions of a user profile
management through firm and user
management, right?
Like we're going to build the preference
management on top in Q1,
notifications also come in Q4, Q1,
and then workflow is just...
kind of a starting point. Again,
we need all of our tools more or less
facilitate requests.
It's not just user access.
All the stuff that you actually submit to
get processed into the book of record,
we call them requests because you
actually have to create an intake for it.
You have to validate,
you have to process it,
you have to make sure you actually submit
it,
and you actually have to make sure it's
coded correctly.
Right? So, so for us,
workflow is a pretty important common
component as part of our kind of,
I'm going to call it the common or the
foundational services.
So this is really part of driving
consistent platform experience.
That's why you see in the documentation,
I actually distinguish,
there's a whole set of platform
management capabilities,
which is the stuff here.
And then there is platform experience
capabilities, which is this stuff here.
There are two massive areas of the
platform,
like the two core pillars of our platform.
This is more app integration, SPOG.
I don't know where I was going with this.
Maybe we kind of ignore it for a second.
I understand, you know,
we know for white labeling,
so if a firm wants to personalize its
inside the compass,
they can use their brand labeling,
you know, yeah, things like that,
so they should be able to customize it.
Yeah, you're right,
but that's not where I was going.
It should probably be over here. Okay.
I did this like April last year,
so I don't remember. No,
the conversation was actually this was
how do you host the apps,
and then this was specific integration
capabilities to bring in third-party apps.
Oh yeah,
that's what I remember now because I saw
white labeling. I'm like, okay,
that's like white labeling. Yes,
it exists on the platform.
It's actually a service, a common service.
It's a platform configuration you can do.
But what we're really seeing,
what I'm really seeing here is the
ability to pass context to other
applications to bring, again,
to draw consistency, right?
So if the core platform.
compass is white labeled,
you have like white label parameters.
Well,
if you have another app that is
pretending to be in the ecosystem,
because that's for some apps we want it
that way,
we should actually have the ability to
pass white labeling context to that app
to consume. So when you render it, oh,
you know, IPC, which is our...
I think our only white labeling client
for some reason,
everybody else dropped off the list.
But IPC decides to configure their
platform with their IPC logo,
with their IPC color and styling,
which is what they do in Compass today.
We can actually pass that into other apps
to say, if you're, especially in SSO,
if you're in the third party app.
and you have to open a new tab, well,
you're going to land somewhere else.
That experience is going to be
inconsistent unless we give you some
stuff, right?
And that stuff could be white labeling.
It could be a specific firm and user
context. Technically,
white labeling is part of firm context.
User context could be language settings,
right? That's the only thing we have.
There might be more.
at some point in the future,
but we want to make sure that this,
there's an ability as we kind of either
do the SSO, as we do the app integration,
that the app has the ability to receive
all this information and we,
as producers of that information,
have the ability to pass it as part of
our app integration,
which starts to get a little bit into
some of the things we want to define.
I'm not.
I'm not sure how much Infinite has done,
to be honest with you.
I think we need to audit it a little bit.
Like, I don't know,
they do language context.
Yes, they do. Maybe. Okay.
In terms of the app,
can you bring me an example?
You mean the third party app or you mean,
because I want to understand that.
When you say app,
is it the app that has been acquired by
National Bank? Yeah.
And it's under its acquisition,
or you're saying something that is a
third party app,
we don't have any control over that,
and they want to.
come and be hosted under this platform?
Yeah, it's a good question.
I think I use app really loosely.
It's any module that we have.
It could be third party that we acquire
ourselves.
It definitely is not complete outside.
We don't have an open marketplace,
if that's what you're thinking. Yeah.
Yeah,
because when we come to the third party,
maybe our...
permissions and all rules would be
limited because there are some things
that make sense. For example,
how to interact, how the security works,
but in terms of dictating rules to the,
you know, internal
Working of the apps,
it's not something that everybody accepts,
correct? And yeah, yeah, so we'll get,
so hold that thought for maybe session
five or six,
we're gonna get into platform
integrations, because like we, yeah,
because of that reason, well,
it's just normal if you work with a SaaS,
there's only so much you can negotiate in
terms of those changes.
If it's in-house, a little bit better,
but it depends on where in-house,
like some other teams,
like even in other parts of wealth,
like we talked about fun facts.
Fun fact is fun fact.
You're not changing it. Yeah, right.
And so there's almost like a grading of
the level of integration that you can
feasibly have as well as what we want to
have. And those two have to come together.
What we want to have might be more than
what the provider can do,
or it might be less than what the
provider can do.
What we want would typically be driven by
how close do we want that experience to
fit with our core application suite,
and how complex is it to control it as
well,
and how strategic is that relationship
even, right?
So you don't want to go through a whole
integration project only to find, oh,
this provider is a little ******.
I want to kind of end my contract with
them.
if throwing that whole thing in the bin.
If it's a strategic relationship and
those capabilities that we require are
pretty close to the core,
we might want to say we want to do more
than just an SSO.
We want to actually embed you as a module
within as part in different parts of the
experience and you don't even know, right,
as a user that it's in a third party.
That's very, very costly.
That's not what something everybody can
do,
but if they get into a strategic
relationship with us and we want to drive
that experience on the platform,
then we're going to commit to a higher
degree of integration. Yeah,
but we'll get into the integration
securing for sure.
But that's what I was trying to explain
here in a really terrible way slash.
That.
Yeah, Graham,
slash having all the kind of the
experience components that Owen actually
manages be part of that conversation,
because again,
the higher the higher order integration
you go,
the more and more you get need to
leverage standards that we have
established,
which is around the design system,
around our information architecture,
around...
the UI frameworks that we use, right?
So that again,
the platform can maintain its consistency.
We don't have a lot of those,
the need for those.
It's typically like servicing is a really
good example.
We want to do that for core services and
not much else.
And even within core services,
is it really core, core adjacent?
I can talk about that too in a minute.
Okay,
I'm going to move away from this diagram
now.
I had a totally different trail of
thought when I was doing this.
But when we talk about platform,
that's what platform really means, right?
Digital, kind of,
you're really building that digital
experience layer for app hosting.
And depending on the type of app,
you're going to present it in a different
experience.
And then you're going to control it all
through platform management and platform,
like kind of platform services.
Okay, I'm going to move on.
So, okay, so I want to kind of get into,
well, what about the apps themselves?
Because as I mentioned here, right,
there's,
we have a core app suite and then we have
like the non-core,
which is stuff that we bolt on top.
And the problem with having a
one-size-fits-all approach here is the
usage patterns are really different.
And at the end of the day,
this is a platform for our firms.
And so we have to fit their needs.
Historically, in some of our, I guess,
in all of our legacy platforms,
we kind of do it and don't do it in
different ways. But ultimately,
If we think about kind of our role in
firm and user management is to drive
effective distribution of those features
and to make sure we control the
permissions and access appropriately to
those features, well,
we have to do it at the right level.
It can't be too broad where it's like,
this is a platform, all or nothing.
If you get a log in, you get everything.
You can't do that, right?
But it also can't be too granular where
it's like,
every time you set up a user,
you have to like configure like 200
things for that user.
That's also a little bit insane. I mean,
you can if you want to,
but I'm not sure if we want to go down
that path. I can. Sorry? Again. Again.
I think it's about, like,
it's about 200 things, right?
Like in Old Compass.
So we kind of said, well, I kind of said,
like, how do we make that better?
And actually,
the more important thing was how do we
make it consistent?
Because reasons why we had issues with
slicing,
feature slicing permissions before was
I'm not sure if we managed the right
level of granularity of permissions,
right? So.
If you think about how our firms actually
work,
I'll skip all this text because I think
the picture says 1000 words.
But let me just remember what I wrote
here. This is yesterday now.
I can't remember what I did yesterday.
Yeah,
do you remember we had the conversation,
Ali, about how, like,
the different types of friends we have,
like, you know, with IBs, we have PMs,
we have big ones, we have, yeah,
we have big, we have small, so ultimately,
so, like,
why is it was hierarchy is parent-child,
correct?
So,
so we have we have firms of all shapes
and sizes, and so we actually have,
if you remember this,
different firm segments, right?
Remember this? Yeah.
And based on different firm segments,
they're organized differently,
their needs are slightly different.
Some of it require some of them come to
us and they want more flexibility in the
platform, some of them don't,
just give me the thing and don't.
Let me tinker with it because I just want
to get on with my day. Right?
We have we have a range of different firm
types, right?
And based on not the same as firm type
like IP versus PM,
different types of firms.
And based on that,
and based on how they're actually
organized,
they might want to actually assign users.
compass features differently.
So what I did here, I tried my best,
it looks a little crazy,
but it all makes sense at the end is I
tried to kind of document, well,
what does a large,
what does a typical firm actually look
like?
Because the way they set up compass would
actually be based on how they're
organized. Like, you know, like,
it's like us here, right? Yeah.
You're allowed to access certain things.
You're definitely not accessing the risk
management tools because you're not at
risk, you're in product.
Right.
Enterprise clients are exactly the same.
It's B2B, right?
So firms have their own organizational
structures and actually they configure
Compass based on that structure. Right.
So that's why we focus on that structures.
If I look at a typical broker,
which is a little bit from a PM,
so I distinguish the two.
I look at how they're organized.
Not everybody is organized exactly like
this, especially if they're small.
If they're big,
then they start to specialize in.
to departments,
but main departments that work with NBIN
from a brokerage perspective typically is,
well,
you actually have the actual advisory
network.
A lot of them just need access to
accounts and clients, right,
to know what's going on and what
transactions have taken place or to even
initiate transactions on the platform.
And so, you know,
typically a large broker would have their
front office teams, which is sales,
business development,
or the advisory network.
I leave things that are like they don't
use Compass.
I leave those functions off this map
because then this would go too crazy.
Typically,
that's like we call it front office
because they're client facing, right?
So they do all of the kind of investor
interactions.
There's a group of people there.
within advisor networks and teams.
Obviously,
they're made-up of advisor and assistants.
Advisor manages people's money and
accounts, so they need access to accounts,
right, to be able to maintain it.
Within the accounts that they're supposed
to manage, because as an advisor,
if you're sitting somewhere,
you probably shouldn't see your peers'
accounts. They're not yours. Like,
he's managing them, right? So
you really should be looking at the list
of accounts that you manage or basically
the list of clients that you manage.
So you come on to the Oracle,
based on the Oracle, yeah,
you would be assigned one or more of
those, right?
And so when you get into Compass, really,
you get to see client account profiles
because those are your clients, right?
You perform your annual kind of review
with them.
You help them facilitate a discussion on
transactions and all that fun stuff,
right? Like.
If it is still a discussion on investment,
you give them advice.
And so you come to Compass to mainly live
in clients and accounts,
but you're able to help them do things
like place trades,
which is why an advisor typically comes
into Compass. You can manage everything,
but only for the Rs that you own.
An assistant in that environment also
does the same thing because they
Let's face it,
the advisors are not actually doing the
administration where they have the
assistance to help them with that.
But assistance can actually support
multiple advisors, right?
Because the operational work,
you can probably slice it up to multiple.
So you might have assistance supporting
multiple,
and so you end up with multiple R codes.
doing the exact same thing and then
showing them and kind of providing
reporting and giving them, you know,
taking in the request and whatnot.
And so you typically see a setup to say,
okay, they can manage everything,
but it's more than what an advisor would
manage.
They might have multiple Oracle designed
to their profile.
We then get into the middle office,
which is a typical broker function
because remember.
they're responsible for their own
accounts in IB land. So compliance, risk,
they manage it all. PM, remember,
we manage that, right?
So a middle office function,
I don't know if you're familiar with this
terminology, it's risk and control. Right?
So, well, if you get big,
there's like 1000 of these people.
Are they on site? Are they compliant?
Are they doing the right things?
Are they doing suspicious things? Well,
you got to put in a layer to provide
oversight for that.
We're regulated at the end of the day.
You have to have oversight, right?
So you would have in most large brokerage
organizations,
whether it's part of operations or it's
standalone function in its own right,
depends on which firm you talk to.
They would typically have a middle office
that reviews transactions,
that looks at reports,
that looks at kind of monthly volumes,
and are there suspicious activities
coming out, right? That sometimes,
if an advisor wants to do things above a
certain threshold, so.
If you're moving like a 10, 1, 5,
10 million bucks for a client, okay,
that's a really large amount.
Let's make sure you understand source of
funds.
Let's make sure you understand what's the
client intent.
Let's make sure it's not money laundering,
right?
So you might have a risk management team
that actually approves these large
transactions.
coming from the front office.
These guys obviously need quite different
tools, right, than the front office.
You need the approval tools.
If the firm is set up where they want to
intervene at a certain,
like above a certain threshold,
usually it's like moving money.
That's the only place we have it in the
platform today.
But you might also want to access data
and reports to review transactional
activity or to review like client
activity, right? Similarly, compliance,
same thing, right?
Like risk and compliance or different
compliance is to make sure you're
conforming, right? So depending, again,
depending on how the firm is set up,
it might be one team, it might be two.
Like if they get really big,
I think we have specialized departments.
who just do like regulatory compliance
all the time, right,
and do reporting all the time.
But you can see that based on that, well,
maybe they need to compass for some data
and reporting access,
only they don't really care about getting
into, do you have a beneficiary named in,
you know, like, like account holder A,
right? They don't care about that. Well,
you get into,
so if you have the sales part, where your
dealing with investors, right?
And then you have the middle part,
which means these guys are kind of on
side.
You also then have an operations team
typically that either kind of supports
these guys' activities.
If it gets like it gets really big,
if you have a national network like
Industrial Alliance and you've got like
branches all over the place and people
are very decentralized and again,
IPC is the same thing.
You've got about 1 to 2000 advisors.
Some things are just more efficient if
you centralize them, right?
So if everybody, you know, if everybody,
especially depending on the type of
broker you are,
if you take on a lot of the operations
yourself, because remember,
they can choose which service, yeah,
right? They, they call management,
that's right, yeah,
they can choose which services they want
to.
they want BNI to provide versus what they
want to do themselves for a very, very,
very large broker.
We only have one of them, right? But like,
it's called a type 4 broker.
They open their own accounts.
And so we're not supporting that account
opening.
They are doing the account opening for
these folks here to either finish the
paperwork to.
process if there's missing information to
do follow up,
maybe to chase after transfers.
If you're trying to move money for an
investor from institution one to
institution B,
horrendous process in Canada. No,
like it's terrible.
It takes forever and you always have to
follow up.
And so there's a team of people,
staff just to follow up transfers.
more and more often than not,
we even have our team ourselves to do
that work and then even operations as a
team to do that work, right? And so again,
if you're in operation or if you're
supporting clients on the operational
follow-ups, again,
you're going to need something very
specific in the system.
Sometimes our firms get so big that they
have full teams of people.
tucked under one service or even
self-service.
So if I'm a team that just manages, say,
transitions, right,
which is helping an advisor move from one
firm to me,
there's a whole process around that. Well,
because how are the clients going to come
over? They're on a different,
possibly a different book of record.
Their assets are in another company,
right?
They got to move over here and they're
going to do it in bulk.
How do I facilitate that? Well,
I need very specific tools.
tools and I only need those tools.
I don't need to trade.
I'm not gonna get trading, right?
I am employed to do transitions,
so I'm gonna be all over transfers, right?
And I'm gonna be all over kind of like
account opening.
I'm gonna do those things.
So you'll see that large broker functions,
their specializations in the specific
features.
even out of the core product suite that
they might want to say, I only need those.
Don't give that employee anything else if
it's not their job, right?
Same thing with trade support, right?
Again, they only do with trading.
They don't deal with account.
Don't give them account opening.
They shouldn't see anybody's SIN numbers.
Like they're not dealing with that.
That's a risky thing.
Like there's no reason for it.
You don't have a,
you don't need a SIN numbers to transact.
So instead of giving your client account
profile,
I'm just going to give you orders.
And I'm going to give you only eligible
orders that you can support,
order types that you can support,
because not everybody can trade
everything, right?
You're kind of licensed to trade mutual
funds,
or like most people can buy mutual funds,
not everybody can buy equities.
Most people can buy equities,
not everybody can sell options, right?
And then some firms just, okay,
you got the three,
I don't want you touching fixed income,
so you're not going to have that, right?
And then even less firms do new issues.
And so again,
granularity of access depending on what
the firm
you know,
the employees actually have to do is what
we see as the demand on how we want to
structure the platform.
There's even technology teams, right?
Like you get big enough,
you have your own IT team.
Like smaller firms, they have one IT guy,
even smaller firms,
the one guy does everything and runs
everything on spreadsheets.
But once you get to a super large broker.
We actually deal with their technology
team,
like where their IT and they look to us
to be their IT kind of thing, right?
So in that scenario,
you have people that might specialize in
doing user access,
because that's an IT function.
The security store.
The security store for large firms,
for large firms, when they specialize,
right? So they might actually have a guy,
and like Harbor Fund is a really good
example, they do actually have one guy.
called Aaron,
who his whole job is user access across
all of their tools, not just Compass,
but all of their tools.
And they've got like 30,
40 tools that I assign,
and then he does the administration for
all of it. That's all he needs access to.
He doesn't need anything else on the
platform. I just need to go in,
create user request, track it,
make sure it's completed,
test that it works. Okay,
I'm going to give it to that advisor
who's starting with us.
job done. They might also run projects,
like if you know,
they bring on their own technology
solutions,
they might want to integrate with us.
And so we,
this is actually Graham's world, right?
Like we're on strategic initiatives,
they might actually want to do plan
projects with us and we help them do that.
And then, you know,
they also have their IT support teams,
right,
where it's getting system events because
they manage incidents and incident
communications and they monitor SLAs and
all that fun stuff or
Again,
access operations gets funneled into here.
Firms are big enough that they have their
own teams to do that. And again,
that defines that.
I put global admin here, Candi,
don't assign people with global admin.
I'm just kind of conceptually saying that
maybe there's somebody, you know,
there might be people who needs to get
access to everything,
just like your production support team
needs to get access to everything.
but that is not an external profile.
I think it's a little bit too risky. So,
broker side, very, I guess,
main take away is depending on, like,
because our brokers get so big,
because they're very, you know,
they're very like, like, branchy,
retail-y, right?
So they have a lot of presence everywhere,
and so they, you know,
their business is all about scale.
is you get a lot of specializations in
the broker world. You have like,
you have one person actually kind of
actually maybe just one guy doing that
ball, so one gal, right?
You might have like two or three people
doing that for trade support.
You have literally one person doing this
and you have like a couple of like one
person who just does approve things all
day and does monitoring.
and then supporting like a pretty wide
base of advisors.
And so our model needs to accommodate for
that granular level of control to say,
you can grab a bunch of things and put it
together based on your business model.
That's great. Sorry, before going further,
in terms of the core features.
If this enterprise comes to us and say,
I want to use your account management,
but I will bring my own, as, let's say,
trade management tool. Okay, in terms
of integration,
they are going to enter from Compass X to
use our OSS for accounts management.
But at the end of the day,
they have to integrate their order
management to our OSS from another
channel.
Is that right? That's right,
because in terms of the interrelationship,
this enterprise need to do have all four
core features in one place, otherwise,
yeah, the business doesn't work, correct?
And so we get into the conversation about
which way, like,
so from an experience perspective and
most importantly from a data.
perspective,
like a like data and actions perspective,
those two things have different paths.
And when we talk about compass,
our focus is obviously on if a firm says,
I need even like everything in one place
so that an advisor is not confused about
what they need,
then we have a specific integration
discussion about that.
And then another conversation we would
have on top,
which we don't do right now because we
don't have the API marketplace is, well,
if you execute something from somewhere
else,
I want it to show up the same everywhere.
That's an API integration problem, right?
It's not a front end integration problem.
So we have two, you're right,
we have two categories of integration
problems.
The compass side of it solves for the UI.
UX integration doesn't mean in the back
it talks to everything.
If they want true seamlessness,
which is why we have that kind of the
tier strategy of we need a data platform,
we need the API integration on top of it,
and then we need the compass platform on
top of that,
is that API layers should kind of work
the same even if they're completely
different.
They should kind of work the same.
from a data timeliness, accuracy,
integrity perspective.
So when you do an API integration,
it still shows up in another place.
That's true integration from a firm's
perspective, right?
But they don't say it like that,
but we know it's like, oh,
I gotta reconcile this platform with this
booking. Now, yeah,
you got an integration problem.
Okay,
and we actually have firms that ask us
for those things too. That's why we have,
we call them you here,
we call them SSO firms,
is we actually have industrial alliance
and all large workers.
If you imagine Compass,
as a operational basic administration
platform.
This thing does not do financial planning.
right?
We don't offer financial planning as a
course service. We're A custodian.
We deal with all your operations, right?
We make sure your accounts are open.
We make sure they're intact.
We make sure the assets are accounted for.
We make sure we present you with all the
transactions that you did on those
accounts. That's record keeping.
That's the basis of our business.
Our business is not to sell financial
advice.
That's the, that's our, like,
that's these firms, that's our clients,
our clients do that, right?
So there's a whole layer of tools that
they need above and beyond COPRESCOCHEF,
right? To say, well,
if I'm going to help somebody with
financial planning,
you really need a tool to do that.
Otherwise,
you can't run planning scenarios, right?
You can't do it on,
I tried doing it on a spreadsheet,
you can't do it on a spreadsheet.
There's no way.
Like you don't know, like,
are you going to run out of money before
you die? No, you can't figure that out.
You got to Monte Carlo that, right?
So these advisor teams,
when they get really, really big,
they have financial planning tools,
they have sales tools.
They got to keep track of who, you know,
like,
it's a business at the end of the day,
right?
Advisors need to keep track of who
they're calling, who are their prospects,
right? Like, what's their pipeline?
right? They got to keep track.
So they need a CRM,
they need a financial planning tool.
Typically,
they need a research tool as well for
investment strategies, right?
So there's a whole bunch of stuff.
And then even kind of like regulatory
reporting compliance,
they need some of that too.
And so that whole ecosystem of stuff,
we don't offer yet. When we do,
maybe it's a little bit different.
They have procured it over the years
themselves. And one firm that we have,
Industrial Alliance, they are, again,
they're our biggest.
They've even gone even one step further
to say,
not only am I going to need to provide my
advisor teams with tools,
I need them again, like Compass.
all in one place because discoverability
is hard. Nobody knows where anything is.
There's different ways of accessing
everything.
So they actually built their version of
Compass for their advisors,
which is called AX360. It's a real thing.
It's live right now.
And in AX360 are all the different entry
points.
So they've done their own SSO into
everything.
And so when they came to us,
they kind of said, you know what,
we need to SSO into compasses. Yeah,
they need to come to us.
So we call that external SSO for the back,
for better or worse, that term.
So that's a type of integration that we.
Have not fully supported yet because we
like the initial one was,
it's same as all the stuff that you saw
so far. You know, here's the plan,
gets architecture got convoluted,
started cutting corners,
and now it kind of works,
but it kind of doesn't. So,
but but it it's it is a it's another
revenue opportunity for us.
is to allow that kind of bespoke external
SSO to come into Compass as a form of
integration.
They usually people don't want it the
other way around because you're thinking,
well, okay, you come into Compass,
but then I have to hide the trade
management.
Do I have to then supplement it with
their third party,
which is still Compass doing an SSO to
that so then they can see it in one place
and to swap the navigation out right for
that third party?
We're not, we're not, we don't,
we don't support that well. And honestly,
again,
I think one firm asked for it a couple
years ago,
and then they went down the same path as
Industrial Alliance.
So Wellington Altus did kind of explore
at the time with a different CIO.
They have a head of technology,
we were talking and they said, oh,
you already have Compass.
Compass looks configurable.
instead of me building my own platform,
why don't I get you to do the all our
SSOs for us into our third party systems?
And then we said, well,
that's a terrible idea because now we
have to do something custom for you and
nobody else is asking for it.
And then three strategy kind of cycles
later for them,
they decided to use Investissements
instead.
So that's then that's their advisor
platform. And then now they're asking for.
that platform SSO into us,
which is much easier to manage on both
accounts.
We don't like the idea of having us
manage the container for the firms. Yeah,
I understand.
In terms of for this line of business,
if we manage to complete the feature
management,
Uh, what we are right, yeah,
these days are working.
If it goes to production,
then SSO to SSO can be manageable. Yeah.
And even they don't need to go to our UI
to select which feature,
because under SSO, they can have scope,
and in that scope, they can pass.
all the entitlements and features they
want and that's going to be probably,
but simple water. Well,
we've gone through the debates about that
and what goes into the token and what
comes to us and it's possible.
It's possible. Yeah,
I mean technically not.
Yeah, yeah, but now that, like,
now that you've done, like,
'cause we've done now the, like, so this,
this initial SSO was actually done like 2
years ago, Candi, a year and a half,
two years ago, it was a long time ago,
long time ago, yeah,
we've been like struggling with this
thing, and at the time, we, we didn't,
we didn't fully explore how that SSO was
gonna work, so we're like, let's do the...
Basics,
let's do a just-in-time identity
provisioning,
which does not include access
provisioning,
because we didn't know how to tell people,
explain these packages to them, right?
So we couldn't do that,
and the process was coupled together.
This is where Candi can really tell you
the details, and then Owen as well,
and then so we never really,
we never went as...
that far,
where it is like minimum MVP was they
don't have to log in to Compass.
That was it.
So then that's an identity provisioning
problem, right?
And the identity linking problem.
So we dealt with that. But yeah,
I'm pretty sure if you ask Industrial
Alliance,
they don't really want different places
to manage their users. Of course,
nobody does.
That's why we're even consolidating on
our side.
But the trick for you is how big is that
demand? Right? It's one firm. I mean, yes,
it's our biggest firm, but it's one.
Who else is asking for it?
Well,
we haven't offered external SSO to
anybody else yet.
So until I think until I think until you
can mature that offering a bit and then
you get now, OK, 5, 6, 7 firms are on it.
I think now you can assess whether that's
important.
What I see from my eyes is that,
not in terms of the request,
in terms of the architecting the platform,
I understand that whenever we grow,
you know, horizontally,
feature management, from my perspective,
is.
In compass X is horizontally, OK,
horizontally, but SSO is vertical, OK?
So SSO should be should be supporting
whatever is inside the feature management.
It means that, OK.
where SSO version 2 didn't have feature
management, but SSO version 3,
now that feature management has been
rolled out, it should support.
whatever is inside the feature management
in terms of the context, you know,
they are loosely coupled, you know,
from architecting point of view, not,
I'm not saying everything from
technically, but yeah,
this is my understanding.
Yeah, it's there's a lot of gaps, like,
because anytime you don't have that
coupling,
it's somebody manually doing something to
reconcile, right?
And so that that is the reality for sure.
You'll find,
and Candi will enlighten you on how many
of those realities we have,
and then you're gonna prioritize it. Okay.
This might end up at the bottom of your
list. Because it like, yeah,
you're like the principle is like the way
to think about it. It is good principle.
That's why,
that's why the UAR conversation is so
hard.
Because what if we started with feature
management first, five years ago,
we would not be having this conversation,
right?
The package creation for firm users,
that would have been automated.
But we didn't do it that way.
We started with the login,
started with the login,
and then we went to drive the RBAC model.
That was the big piece.
And then we got stuck in the RBAC model.
And then so we didn't get time to say,
okay, how do you do feature management?
How do you do proper feature kind of
permissioning and data permission
together?
And how do you package that for a user
and a firm?
We didn't get that far.
We had the pieces of it, right? So no,
you can note that down in your backlog,
but there's probably like you'll come
across a big list and it was spending the
time to build that list with Candi
because we have a lot of gaps.
This is not the only one. But yeah,
it's the right line of thinking in terms
of the capability assessment.
Yeah, wait, we're gonna, don't worry,
we'll do a,
I think there is a KT on all the gaps we
have at some point.
We're working on it, right, Candi?
We can go back in history,
we can actually pull up aha,
like the whole kind of all the stuff we
shipped,
and then we can look at everyone and it's
like,
what corners did we cut for this epic?
And you go through 30 of them.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm building the visual sheets.
Nice. Yeah, we're doing it.
Candi and I are helping kind of you with
the documentation on both sides.
She's kind of coming in from a bottom-up
product capability assessment.
I'm going to do the top-down business
contact.
You're going to meet in the middle,
and then it's the crap in the middle.
That's a good update.
KING.
Okay,
so I did another one just as another
example to say, well,
firms are just different.
It really depends on how they're
organized. Like, like, you know,
if you build a company,
you have your own vision, right?
And you have your own vision of how you
delegate work.
And so there's differences in broker
world.
There's also differences in the PM world.
I'm not saying that PM and brokers are
intrinsically different because some
firms actually,
like their organizational structure,
looks exactly the same,
even though they are different types of
businesses.
So if you get big enough as a PM,
you actually kind of start to look like a
broker. Right? Nicola,
who is the biggest firm on our books,
actually,
I'll get into this first and I'll get
into the examples,
so they have it down below.
I forgot I did that.
With with a with a typical PM,
the job the job is very similar.
The only change is that they're
discretionary. Remember,
they they they they take they take
investment decision on behalf of the
client, right?
So you don't have any of that like on
this side, you know,
advisors are providing advice.
I'm waiting for the client to tell me
what to do.
So there's a lot of client and investor
interaction.
There's a lot of investor support,
investor calls, hey, you know,
I need to do this. And then you translate.
So there's a lot of traffic going on over
there. Here, not really, right?
Very different. In the PM space,
very similar structure you'll see across
a number of PM firms.
You'll have,
you'll still have the front office,
which is maintaining client relationships
and sales, but you're not a scale,
like you're not a scaling business if
you're a PM.
If you're a portfolio manager,
you typically are managing kind of ultra
high net worth clients or family offices.
Like, you know,
you got like a small group of people
would typically give you a lot of money.
And so there's not a ton that comes out
of technology needs in the front office
for a PM,
and actually across the board in a PM,
because the business is actually a lot
simpler.
The complexity comes from the investments,
right? So everything else is simpler.
So you'll have.
a front office, you know,
you'll have people who manage sales or
client relations.
You're going to see that maybe not
everybody gets into Compass, right?
Because if I'm trying to maintain
relationships with you at the end as the
investor,
I need to understand all the information
about you.
It's going to be again in my whatever.
CRM tool or my portfolio management
system is what typically happens. I'm not,
I don't actually need to get into like
specific client profiles.
I don't need to go into Compass and look
up all that information about you because
that information is largely irrelevant to
the client anyway.
You're not going to look at the orders
that you placed.
You're not going to go into a client
profile. Oh, I'm talking to you.
Let's see what you did in the last
quarter.
They don't make those decisions, you do.
So, well, like, so you as an investor,
you don't make those decisions, I do. So,
I'm not gonna tell you,
I'm not gonna give you a transaction
report, that's irrelevant.
I'm gonna tell you how your portfolio is
doing, right? Yeah. And then I'm gonna,
so my conversations are a little bit
different and so my tooling is different,
right? So, here.
We don't see a lot of that in Compass at
most is, you know,
if a client calls and says, hey, you know,
I was gonna take out my 100 grand and buy
a Ferrari, whatever, where did it go?
Like,
that's the only question you're gonna get,
right?
And you're gonna go like very
infrequently,
but you're gonna go into Compass and say,
oh yeah, no, I think it stuck somewhere.
Like, you know,
you're gonna have that conversation.
So very low usage here.
Very, you can see, like,
very different right to the business here,
very simple, very simple. You know,
another front office is like, okay,
you're selling portfolio management,
of course,
you're gonna sell your portfolios, right?
So, typically,
and this is why you hear a lot of people
are still in net rep,
a lot of people are still in net rep,
basically, you know what a lot of...
PMs, all they need is net rep from us.
All they need to do is trade.
And they trade all day, right?
So if you're managing A portfolio,
what is a portfolio?
It's a range of securities, right?
It's a basket of securities that you have.
And the only time you need to trade is,
you know, if I, if you and as an investor,
you come to me and you're expecting to
meet certain goals in, you know,
in your short.
medium to long term.
I just need to make sure you're on track.
And to do that,
I need to make sure the investments are
performing against your goals, right?
So if you want to retire at 50, okay,
we're going to be very aggressive.
And if you, if you, you know,
if you want to make,
we're going to be aggressive,
we're going to be in, you know,
we're going to be in rapid wealth
accumulation mode. So I'm going to,
I'm going to trade a lot and
you know,
invest in a certain profile of securities
that would meet your objectives and I
need to maintain that allocation.
And so every time, you know,
one stock increases,
let's say it's a blue chip stock,
look at that, it's like a, you know,
RBC freaking like triples in two years,
every two years, right?
Because it's a bank stock in Canada,
it goes up, value of RBC goes up. Well,
that means relatively speaking,
the rest of your stocks are actually
lower in the percentage of allocation,
now I need to rebalance.
I need to make sure that if I say 10% RBC,
90% everything else,
I gotta maintain that ratio.
That's the only time you really see PMs
trade is to be able to make sure they
manage that performance of the portfolio
that they're allocating to the client,
right?
And so we do get good trade volume here.
It's not as high as here because again,
you have a million customers on this side
as Industrial Alliance,
you got a million accounts,
you're going to get called every single
day to do something, right?
You're going to get client instructions
to execute on something.
So you're going to see a lot of volume on
this side here.
It's mainly the portfolio management
themselves that trade or again,
if they get big enough, then somebody,
a team actually manages A portfolio for
everybody and then they trade on all the
accounts for everybody.
So you see a lot of trading,
you see a lot of allocations.
And then sometimes again,
investment research is a core part of
making investment strategies.
And so you'll see them subscribe to
research as well.
But very, very simple.
Either they trade or they don't is really
a PM's structure typically.
You'd also see, again, if, you know,
there are some things that you need to do.
You do, like, as a PM,
just like you're an IB,
you're still a wealth management company.
You're regulated.
So you have to do your reporting.
And there are certain regulatory
obligations that you need to meet.
And so you typically do have an
operations and compliance person.
And it's at least one,
because the chief compliance officer role
is actually a regulatory requirement.
That person cannot deal with investment,
so you don't have conflict of interest in
an organization. And so when you go out,
early tomorrow when you start a PM firm,
first person you're going to hire is a
CCO if you're the main portfolio manager,
right?
So this is a minimum and they're
responsible to all the filings and all
the reporting and the governance of what
goes on in here to make sure that you're
always acting in the best interest of
your client because that's your
obligation from a regulatory perspective
and like from an ethical perspective.
Right?
And you also still need to make sure that,
okay, you know,
there's still an element of there's trade,
okay, this trade doesn't have enough cash,
where am I going to get the cash from?
You know,
like there's still a bit of that
management of it,
which is more operational than portfolio.
Yeah. Right. Portfolio,
you want these people specializing in
investments.
operations,
you want people specializing in the
administration. Yeah, right.
So these are the guys we talk to all the
time on the PM side because again,
they still use Compass to do everything
apart from training. Yeah, right.
And what about the reconciliation?
What is the reconciliation here?
A lot of things, but at minimum,
a good example of a recon job is a PM is
actually obligated to make sure that when
they execute trades,
the trades are kind of, you know,
like the source of truth is on their side,
right?
They have to make sure they're executed
properly and it reports back.
When you trade as a PM, remember,
you can trade anywhere.
Right, you don't have to trade with us.
You can trade with like 3 custodians,
or you can trade with like different
desks that settle with us,
where you can trade in an external venue
and settle back with us. Well,
who's keeping that traceability?
It's not NBIN.
They got to keep track of it.
Ohh, right. So, so they have like a big,
big recon that they're obligated to do as
a PM is trade reconciliation. So,
it's offline.
It means that when they submit a trade,
for example, by NVIDIA stock, yeah,
they don't,
they're not obligated to do it real time
in our OSS, right?
They can do it anyway.
End of A or end of B, whatever they want.
Yeah, well, any venue they want,
and venue means like market,
and it could mean any broker that they
want.
So you can train in Bloomberg if you want,
and that gets routed to somebody who's
not an BNI, like they don't need to.
They don't need to kind of go into our
order book. They can go into Fidelity.
They can go into just some random third
party,
but then they have to provide instruction
that they settle back to their custodian.
of choice, right?
And so we don't know the decisions.
They may all we see is a settlement.
So we provide that to say, yep,
we got your trade.
It's come in from somewhere.
And then here's a reporting for it.
Now it's your job to reconcile that with
your intent was.
And you have to do that every day.
That's wonderful.
Welcome to the finance social services
infrastructure. And in terms of the SLA,
what I understand is that the market
starts from East Hemisphere to, you know,
the West Hemisphere.
It came from Australia to, you know,
to Banque work.
Time's up.
Our SNA is like that, that should be 24 7.
No, we don't, like for us, we don't,
we don't, we only do Canadian and US.
We don't do anything else. Oh,
we just North America market. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah,
they gotta go elsewhere if they want to.
which is a gap in the offer.
But not, not, not, not digital,
not digital, yeah, it's core feature,
but not digital offering.
It's like the actual training service
offering is not there.
Like the digital typically follows, right?
What the service can provide. And so,
yeah, like we can turn on 24 by 7 trade.
All we need to do is just.
Like, remove the validations in the UI,
where it just, yeah, but you're graded,
but then nothing gets processed because
we don't support it. Thank you.
Questions? Questions, Candi?
I'm just thinking, we only support TSX,
right? So TSX are platforms, and DTCC,
yeah, US side, yeah. So,
that's no meaning open 24, exactly,
because the market's closed, yeah.
So we actually put the market.
close,
you can't place trades anymore at 4:00
and ring the bells, yeah, exactly.
Okay,
so I thought I would just draw like a
schedule, like an actual example of each.
We don't need to go too much into,
but it's just to reinforce that concept
of when you look at specific brokers,
okay,
even our two largest ones in IPW and
Harborfront,
they're organized a little bit
differently.
You'll see that, at a high level,
they actually have a similar like
structure to kind of my template here,
but specifically in the ops,
'cause we deal mostly with the ops people
here,
they might be just organized a little bit
different, right? Like, ops still,
we still, yeah, we still,
you skip the easy PM stuff,
so you didn't miss all that much.
We're now talking about, well,
what this like,
like let's talk realistic example.
We have Industrial Alliance.
We won't get too much into these guys
because we mainly deal with the ops from
a compass perspective.
They're just a little bit different to
say another broker, right?
They decides that they actually have an
ops team that does both.
kind of the monitoring, right?
Like the monitoring,
you can call it the risk management part,
and the operations part,
and their operations is actually client
support, client servicing,
or advisor support, advisor servicing.
And so you'll have somebody specializing
in all inquiries related to new accounts
and account opening.
Her name is Carol.
She deals with new accounts.
And so she doesn't talk to us much
because they use their own account
opening solution.
But from an account like maintenance
perspective,
she like she always wants to know what's
going on.
And so you'll see that her team and
herself really only cares about account
management functions.
You'll have another person here called
Karine who manages a lot of like, well,
she actually oversees all advisor support,
but heavily focused on advisor servicing.
issues because of remember the volumes
that we talked about,
high high volumes on the IB side,
just number of sheer number of accounts
and the scaling and all of that,
they get a lot of money movement requests,
they get a lot of reoccurring requests,
like so you want to kind of bank with
these people,
they're going to convince you,
which is the right thing to do is.
like consistent investment is better than
lump sum, right?
So you get a lot of reoccurring plan
setups with them.
So there's a lot of transaction
follow-ups that need to take place.
So they put a person in there called
Korean specializing in servicing that.
And then it goes into even some of the
transactions.
And then same thing with trade support.
They have a, it was Richard,
I don't know who the new guy is now.
They have a guy looking after anything
that's execution related, right?
Order execution related.
And so their support for advisors when it
comes to that,
they also aggregate and trade.
They're big enough that, you know,
they dictate where they want to trade
based on the pricing and whatever is
favorable to that.
And so you have a desk that manages that.
Between the three of them,
three different sets of provisions.
Did you say this was? Carol? Yeah.
And then you see David playing pop up
every now and again on the IT side,
who rolls up to, I think, Adam still,
I can't remember, is it?
Who's there?
I know, I know the,
I know Ray's doppelganger on the IPC side.
I forgot, have you? There's a bunch of,
yeah. Yeah.
It was like Mark's brother works over
there. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. So,
head of Ops in International Alliance is
Mark Robinson. He's about to retire,
so you don't need to remember him, but...
But like, but then contrast that to like,
say, a harbor front, which is a,
we don't like to talk about harbor front
too much. They're too,
they're too crazy for us.
But foundationally, Brent,
who's their head of ops, is back office,
mainly kind of, well,
sort of front office-y.
They do a lot of advisor support
activities.
But one thing that they do,
maybe that's like a little bit different
is the compliance function is outside of
kind of like the account opening and
servicing.
So they have a person dealing with
approvals here. Oh, okay. I forgot.
I think his name is Ian versus.
people who kind of work on like the
similar functions to this, right?
Advisor support,
we talk about advisor transitions.
There's a lady, forgot her name now.
I remember her face,
I don't remember her name.
She oversees advisor transitions,
which is bringing like whole books onto
the platform, onto their platform.
So based on that,
you'll see we're going to assign,
they're going to assign themselves
different things, right? Like this,
this is an extreme case,
like Carol actually sees everything,
like she's not just new account,
but because that's what she wants to,
but her team might be an account opening
specialist.
They only do account management, right?
And nothing else.
They're not allowed to touch it.
anything else. These guys here,
they only do transfers and account
openings. They do nothing else.
So they're not going to see anything else.
If I go to the PM side,
very different story. Like I said,
the structure is really simple.
More often than not,
people kind of look like a COPRESCOCHEF.
Everybody just freaking,
you're either trading or you're not
trading. That's it, right?
It's all or nothing except for the
trading component.
Right, because there's no,
there's no barriers,
there's no segregation,
like you're in the middle,
you're gonna look after everything.
The only difference is if you're a
portfolio manager, again,
responsible for a certain set of accounts,
there might be a limitation on the
oracles that you have access to.
But function, like functions wise,
all the core features,
it's typically all of it.
Right, there's no distinction there.
I stuck a little nice box.
We'll talk about the kind of the
sub-advisory kind of referral set up
later, but with a lot of PM firms,
more so than I think here,
we hear about it more,
the firm relationships
There's a lot more going on on the PM
site.
So I stuck it here just to remind myself
to go over it,
but we'll kind of come back to it during
multi-firm.
But like I said, like,
and then I put in Nicola because,
as I said before, like, these are not,
these are not like, oh,
IVs have to be set up in this way.
It's very, very granular.
And then PMs have to be really,
really simple. No,
like we call them firm segments because
any firm can take up any of this
structure. And so like even a PM,
but we get to a big PM, they get cool,
they're our biggest firm.
they're a PM,
but they kind of are like a broker in
terms of their organizational setup.
They have centralized teams to manage
things because they are big enough to do
that. And so I didn't draw it out here,
but I kind of made a note just to say all
of this to say is we're not
distinguishing,
we're not bucketing firms into their firm
types, that alone.
is not enough for us like to look at kind
of how we offer the flexibility and
features because it just really depends
on the organizational set up the firm,
the size of that firm. Like I said,
Nicole is big enough as a PM.
They don't look like a small PM at all.
They look like not an industrial alliance,
but like a like a smaller size version of
the broker. They have specialization.
Yeah, and they're gonna see it,
like we worked with their account opening
team because they have one, right?
Whereas here,
they're not gonna have an account opening
team. It's like one person,
and I think Diana has Diane has like
three people right in ultimate compliance
on on with are involved. So,
you have you provided a high level?
Of the organization structure, OK,
and you have broken down the entities and
objects, and it depends, for example,
Industrial Alliance has a bigger
complexity for the PMs, it's less, yeah,
then.
And then the examples.
What I want to translate and map it to
what we are doing right now.
It's that package feature registry is the
translation of the features or accesses
that these organizations require.
Okay, behind the curtain,
I mean behind our curtain, not theirs,
we have another one that is package
resources that it translates again the
package feature register into our
resources that those resources.
Are distributed into different multiple
modules and applications? Not quite,
not quite. So,
the feature registry allows us to see the
full universe of exactly how do we.
How do we like, because again,
our core features, like we built them,
right?
So we know what to offer under the
umbrella of services.
It's your structure for us to say,
what's the inventory, right?
That allows me to,
any firm can come to me, as you can see,
there are four very different setups.
Any firm can, I can still.
connect their organizational structure
with the list of features that they want,
right? Because they need that from us.
The feature to resources, well,
the resource is an implementation,
it's a representation of the features,
right?
It's a representation and we bastardize
that representation because we mix in
kind of,
you hear authorization levels with the
actual course screen, the actual feature.
Commissions, right?
So the entitlement is made-up of two
parts,
but they're all resources at the end of
the day. So, to me,
that feature to resource is the
implementation. Sure,
feature is the feature that sees the
model, right?
And then the implementation then is what
gets enforced, though, on the platform,
and so...
resources is really ultimately what
controls access in the platform itself.
You package a bunch of resources together
to say this person has this list of stuff
that they have and that's the
implementation side.
And we do that through firm packages and
user packages.
So user packages and firm packages are
just.
groupings of resources. Okay, yeah, yeah,
that makes sense. Okay, thank you. So you,
like, this is why we struggle, like,
and I made the comment at the beginning
to say we really should have started with
feature management first five years ago,
because there's actually,
if you look and inspect in the platform.
before this discussion,
there is no connection between features
and resources. It's, you have to know.
You just look at the list of resources,
right? And then what we're doing now with,
if we,
I don't think we're gonna get to it,
but like putting a UI on top,
putting an actual representation of the
registry in there,
we're now connecting the dots to say this
feature actually is.
This set is represented by this list of
resources. Yeah,
that's what I am struggling to understand.
Yeah, I know, I know. We can, we can,
we can deep dive more,
but mental model is,
I need us to be at this level first
though, is to understand, yeah, well,
why do we have features defined in a
certain way and how does the platform
organize them?
So knowing this,
this is a really long-winded way of
saying we need flexibility at the right
level, because a really good example,
right?
Like a client support might want to just
manage service request here,
but then this client support guy needs to.
approve servicing request, right?
Same job, same title, different functions.
Yeah.
How do I give this firm manage and then
this firm control? Right?
Standard roles now, you know, don't apply.
That's why RBAC doesn't work for us.
Because I can't say the role is client
advisor support.
Because client advisor support at Harvard
Mend means something completely different
to Industrial Alliance.
And it means something completely
different to RN Croft. Right. Yeah.
And by the way, there's no approve,
remember, in the PM world.
The risk is on us. There are accounts.
And so I can't give Diane over here
approved.
It only lives in the broker build.
Right, so how do I do that? OK, OK,
we're gonna get into that now.
So the solution,
now that we have the problem,
which is you can read through this later.
So the solution is, first of all,
we need a different approach between core
and non-core. If we do this to everything,
non-core is going to be too complicated,
right?
But there is a way we want to think about
the core and the platform needs to help
us enforce that thinking of the core.
If you look at the organization of the
core services that we talked about, right,
so account management, servicing,
orders and trains,
we need that level of granularity to say,
can you view, can you manage,
can you actually approve something?
And I need to be able to specify that per
person.
And sometimes I even need to be able to
say,
does this firm even have the ability to
approve? Because again,
PMs can't approve stuff. We do, right?
We approve the account openings,
like NBI and us, because again,
they're an NBI named those accounts,
right? So how do I do that?
I look to the platform then to be
organized so that all the features that
come into the platform.
must conform to certain standards if
you're building a core service,
and especially like core transactional
service. Everything else we don't care.
Fun fact, like who cares, right?
Like I know it's kind of, well,
but it's an add-on. Anyway. So for me,
I need that flexibility of core services
to come in to say if you're building
something for us and you're building an
account management.
module. First of all,
we know that to do transactional
processing of any request,
you have to be able to view the request,
you have to be able to view the
information surrounding the request,
so like client information,
client contact, all of that stuff.
I have to be able to initiate a change,
right?
Like so if you moved address and I need
to update your,
that's an account management issue.
I have to be able to
Initiate a change of address to like,
so my ability to manage that,
I have to be able to control it in the
platform and have to say, you know, hey,
if you're an advisor.
Let's go back to this because I like this
map. If you're an advisor, you know,
right,
who's managing a bunch of clients or you
are an operations person and, you know,
one of your super wealthy rich clients
moved,
you need to facilitate a change of
address, right?
So you need to go into the system and you
need to be able to manage that client's
profile.
So that's where you get a managed
function. If that change of a profile,
let's say it's super high risk, right?
You move jurisdictions,
you're no longer a Canadian resident,
a whole bunch of other things need to
change. Well, okay, okay, right?
Like where you came into a large body.
Maybe from a risk perspective,
I want to take a look at that and I want
to approve that change.
So now I need to be able to say,
not only does your account management
feature,
if you're building a profile modification
tool for us for NDIN,
you're going to have to give me a view
version of it.
You're not going to have to give me a
manage version of it,
because I need to be able to give any of
these people here the ability to initiate
that.
That, that change, but, but...
I also need you to be able to have
workflow so then I can route it to
somebody to approve that change.
Depending on what it is. So,
and not everybody can approve,
because going back to this,
we own the accounts for the PMs.
We approve.
That request actually goes over to that
side of our floor. They approve it.
So an employee needs access to that tool
to approve,
and they only need access to that.
They don't need access to anything else.
on the broker side,
if they use our solution,
this is the crazy part,
for account management, they're like,
oh yeah, you know,
we'll use MBIN's kind of account
modification capabilities.
We're not going to go directly into the
book of record.
We're not going to commission Aqua or 4Is
or anybody else to do that for us.
We're going to use your tool. Okay.
These people are responsible for their
own accounts.
they have to approve.
So I need to assign Carol the ability to
approve those changes.
So when you build a core feature,
it's actually really important that
depending on the request,
depending on the type of transaction,
depending on the type of change that you
want to initiate, you know,
like Graham is looking at options for us
now, right? For options, well,
you have to apply commissions to options.
That's an action you need to manage.
Not everybody should be able to do that.
It just really depends on who the firm
decides will have that job.
It could be all advisors get to enter in
commissions, right?
I can give it to everybody. It could be,
no,
it's a head office thing because it's a
commission grid, it's a billing thing,
right?
So they want to centralize a couple of
people to do that.
Graham will now have to build an app so
we can view all the options,
positions that.
you know, that are available for that,
that are expiring for that month.
And he needs to build like a managed
resource, right?
I need to be able to the platform for the
platform to tell if this person has the
ability to manage the commissions.
And if there's even an approval,
we don't have that for commissions,
thank God.
But if somebody needs to intervene and
approve those commissions,
which some of our firms might come to us
in the future, well.
That tool now needs a controlled resource.
I need to,
the platform needs to tell that tool,
this person has the ability to approve
commissions, right?
So you need to understand that.
And it's very, I mean,
for all the stuff on Complex,
it's actually very standard.
All transactions have the potential to
have a view manage or control or even.
process. We didn't get into process yet,
but we'll get into process in a second.
That's why we have that standard.
And so when you come to build it out for
us, and at its core,
we have that conversation up front from
an integration perspective to say,
you need to understand these tiers of
access levels,
and I need to tell you what access level
this person has, because...
Compass manages, right? Yeah,
and you'll see that, you know,
we do a lot of the request for them,
but really, we talk, we tweak them.
So, does that make more sense now? Like,
the main is, yeah, but in standard,
you know, terminology or, let's see,
architecture,
we have view and also update.
Date or create, yeah, right, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah,
something that is strange for me is about
the control and process,
which are good questions.
They're right workflows,
but we have converted workflows inside
our, so not quite, yes and no. So,
don't listen to these guys. Sorry,
Kevin joined as well on Graham Pivot.
off to the side because this is related
to a discovery confusion that we have.
We,
when we say somebody has managed and
control, their actual features,
they're not authorization levels.
This is something I have to correct for
GP. These are not like,
because authorization level is right,
right? You get, like you said,
like the standard of scopes is either
your view or you write ****, right?
And then like, you know.
conditional on where,
like you can write different things,
manage control or all different write
functions.
Right, and yeah,
like approval specifically is a workflow
step, right? So, like,
your like the actual function is like
your, you know, your actual task, right?
That stuff, yeah,
that's what it actually is,
and what we're kind of saying in, well,
you saw at the beginning,
we don't have a workflow management
solution, yeah,
so we have to compensate for that somehow.
And there are specific features that need
to be controlled because approval is not
like represented as a workflow,
so you actually need to build a feature
for it in all of our apps.
And so what controls that coarse grain on
that feature is you need a resource to
control that feature.
It's because you're right, like it's not,
I would not interpret manager control.
as different permissions.
They're not the right permissions, right?
You're just writing different things.
In the manage,
you're actually writing the transaction.
In the control,
you're writing up to a workflow step.
And then in process, also, well, kind of,
but process for us, like,
I don't even know why we talk about it,
because like,
we don't have a process anymore.
But process is like,
it's an operational coding, right,
of the transaction. Like,
if you know your request comes in and the
intake validation fails you,
and then the thing doesn't actually get
like straight through processing, well,
somebody needs to code it in.
So that's a processing step, right?
And that's what processing means.
It's the operational process or something
we just.
don't actually have real tools in
COPRESCOCHEF where processing.
That's the only difference, but, but yes,
again,
another workflow step in combination with
a set of write actions for process,
usually. OK, when we say correct,
but when we say control,
what happens in the back end? I mean...
Okay,
you want to approve to do this
transaction.
How we translate it in the back end,
because it depends on the tool,
because we don't have a global workflow
management service, it's all different.
Yeah, just one example I want to get,
you know, for example,
an application in the secure zone,
you know.
What, how you, I mean, how we translate,
I mean, we call an API and say,
for example, in secure zone and say, okay,
for this specific user,
change the flag from zero to 1,
something like that,
because we have to somehow.
personalized, not personalized,
customized per each control. It's, yeah,
is that's right. That's what I understand.
That's what it is today.
It's a customization depending on the app
and how they decided to build it. Oh,
okay. It's not, yeah,
that's why we have this little wonky. How,
okay, sorry.
How they decide to build,
it means that has not been built. No,
like, so servicing is a good example,
because there's tons of servicing
approvals. I don't know, okay.
Maybe I won't pick on Kevin because he's
not feeling well today.
But servicing approvals uses a workflow
solution that's...
fully customized to servicing.
It's a full custom solution, right?
They decided to use this,
I don't know if they moved away from it
yet, but they were going to,
they had implemented Camunda,
which is an open source workforce
management solution,
and they decided to manage all tasks
within that solution.
And so servicing approvals is actually.
a module or like a separate app that
talks to that workflow management layer
to do the whatever they do.
I don't know if it's like a 0 to one.
I don't know what they do.
It's an update to the status of the
request so that it can continue with the
next workflow step.
That's very customized to servicing.
You can't use that.
Nobody else uses that workflow tool and I
think they're actually moving away from
that workflow tool to ServiceNow to
something else.
Right, but...
Whatever that trigger is to continue that
workflow would be different to say an
account opening solution built by our
lovely friends at Broadridge, right?
Because we use that third party tool to
do account opening and within account
building, there's even more,
like there's quite a ton of approvals
that are involved, reviews, approvals,
like four eyes, checks,
like what I forgot.
The term is,
when you do kind of like pre and post
approval reviews,
you would notice the drops and drop, yeah,
like, so there's multiple stages to,
and then if there's if there's a specific
type of application where you know this
account needs to do a bit more,
then you bring in like another set of
like person to.
do specialized approvals for that
particular thing. And that's very,
very much built into the account opening
solution.
So because we don't have this concept of
like a global workflow,
you can't define like approvals in a
consistent way.
And so the best thing we can do is to say,
do you have approval?
features in your system,
I need to abstract that and make sure
that becomes an assignable thing to a
user.
It's not the best solution because you'll
see we run into problems if you have what
happens if you have multiple users. Well,
it's all control, right?
But control at different stages and we
have no way to define it.
We have to define it in the target app.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, good observation.
That's the confusion,
but it's not authorization levels.
It's very different.
We got to set JP right on that.
And now that's why we do the view versus
manage that 10-minute conversation.
Questions?
I'm just curious about going away from
Candi.
We don't we don't ask questions about
what that train does,
because you would you would get into this
very, very dark place very quickly,
and so you kind of back away and let
Kevin deal with it.
Sorry, Kevin.
I thought you said you weren't going to
pick on me today.
But it's so such an easy target.
I know it's so easy.
But even us,
like we try to not question what goes on
in there.
It's that team is doomed for failure.
That's right.
It's for the best for everybody.
Yes, correct. Okay.
So that's why our feature registry looks
like the way it does is because for one,
you know,
we have to register these services as
independent features. So then again,
I come back to here.
My favorite hacking diagram is if one
person wants
to not see account opening,
the other person does, I can do that,
right?
I can have that level of granularity at
the feature level.
And then I can also say, well,
they are actually not in a supervisory
role. They're pure operations.
I'm just going to give them manage,
whereas these guys are supervisory,
I'm going to give them control.
I have to be able to do that as well.
Right,
and so our feature registry reflects that,
and it should reflect, like, you know,
for each module,
what level of access or what type of
access comes with it? Sorry,
what type of controls you have come with
it across account servicing orders and
trades and across view, manage, control,
and agree.
Why we?
destroy process in favor of control if we
don't have it today.
We just don't have features like that
today,
because usually process actually means
like a person logs into the OSS and keys
something in. It's not a compass,
doesn't happen. Oh, okay.
We can provide the utility to do so,
but that's an integration.
If you do the integration, then.
So, I don't know. I think we came,
I don't remember why we came up with this
one. I think there was like 1 feature,
I think. Yeah,
I think there was like 1 feature
somewhere. Only accountable. It's, yeah,
I don't remember.
I don't remember what it was for. CPMC.
Is it CPMC?
Which is our accountable break operations
came downstairs.
If anything falls out of our usual flow,
oh yeah, it's to change the status.
So it's more internal. It's internal,
yeah, most of it is internal,
unless you open your own accounts,
which is like one firm doing that,
which is an industrial alliance.
And if they want to,
I think this is what it's for.
Like, well,
if your account opening paperwork is
missing some stuff and it doesn't STP,
well, what does it do?
It lands on somebody's lap and they're
going to have to review and go, oh,
what's missing? And oh,
if I can back with the information for
you, okay,
I'm just going to take that piece of
information and I'm going to finish
processing it directly into the book of
record, into OSS. And when I do that,
well,
your account opening app is still stuck
in processing, right?
or submitting or error or in review or
something like that in the tool.
As a person who finished your keying in
all your account opening information,
I still have to go back until it set it
to completed.
I think that's the only representation of
processing we have in the system,
because you can't really do anything else.
You still have to go to the source system
to do it.
Because typically what falls into there
is manual intervention.
Somebody needs to intervene. Yeah.
It makes sense, data input, huh,
data input, data input, yeah,
into into a into a source system.
Okay,
so I don't think I'm going to go through
this,
but I think I actually described that
leveling more in here for your reference.
You can skip this for now.
You can skip that. I didn't do the page,
but I tried to do a definition.
Somebody can add the view because I was
doing a shorthand,
never added it when this page got created.
But this is just to kind of explain that
concept in more detail on, hey,
there's some functions.
that line up to the layering that we
talked about, right?
Which happens to be lined to the front
middle back office setup over firm.
Just so you have a more real kind of idea
with stuff in it.
You don't have to worry about this. Again,
I created this for a completely different
purpose.
It was to actually talk about platform
capabilities at the time,
which is no longer required,
but platform capabilities basically need
to apply.
you know, implement, right,
and distribute all these features.
That's why this diagram got created.
But if you want more details around an
example on our client management,
which is the heart and soul of Kevin,
you can take a look at it in here.
I provided a link in the page here.
All right. Last thing I'll mention again,
the optimal,
like I call it the organization of the
core product. So now we know.
Right,
core services inventory needs to be done
at a feature level. That feature,
like when we inventory it,
we need to inventory also what kind of
what things does that app do against kind
of our standard kind of like, I guess,
no mentation of the view manage control
and process.
And the third thing that our platform
also needs to do is, as I mentioned,
like the middle office,
like the risk management and control
stuff.
Really,
those tools are client-facing tools only
for IBs, for the most part,
not for the PMs,
but our internal teams use it as well.
So our platform also needs to be aware
that these tools can be distributed for
internal use and external use.
And then we'll get into the concept now
of packaging.
All of this gets into the concept of...
Why do we have packaging, right?
So before we get into the packaging,
because I don't think that's a today
session, that's the next session.
I also want to touch on, well,
that's great for core.
That's very granular.
And it's very granular because again,
like people interact with BNI on a
day-to-day and our core services in a
very specific way,
depending on their firm's setup.
What about the non-core stuff?
Well,
non-core is not really related to that
core ecosystem.
And if you look at something like
research, which is a non-core, right,
if you look at like the financial
planning tool we talked about earlier,
which is non-core, that usage pattern,
if you look at how that maps to here.
is not as granular and most cases,
it's all or nothing, right?
You either get a financial planning tool
or you get a PM system where you don't.
And I'm not really sure if I care about
what you do in there, right?
As from an MBI perspective, yeah, exactly.
So it's a, like, you know,
the stuff you build on top of the core,
non-core, well.
We don't really care.
We and all of our non-core stuff is
really that upsell,
the value-added services that we have.
The only thing we really want to know is
who has it so we can charge for it, right?
And then obviously usage and all of that
fun stuff, right?
And so for non-core product distribution,
we're not going to be obsessive about
implementing that structure.
because our firms will not ask us for it
and we don't care in return.
So everybody wins with a simple approach.
And so for non-core products distribution,
we still want it on the registry, right?
But it's all or nothing.
It's you have it or you don't,
which means I give you access or I don't.
And the way I give you access is through
our integration discussion.
from earlier.
As long as I bring it into the platform
and I can assign it to you in the
platform,
that's as far as we're going to go.
So here we get into the discussion of in
the platform's way to manage the non-core
products is through our platform
integration playbook.
And which labels of view manage control
of? It's none, because it's...
We don't care.
Ohh, the none, ohh, in the form, yeah,
in the form, yeah, it's none,
or I think Owen changed it to none versus
manage, ohh, but I don't love it,
it should just be you have it or you
don't, yeah,
manage means something very specific for
us, right? So,
we still need to work on the copy for
that, but, but yeah, it's none or...
You have it,
and we need a word for you have it,
maybe fix a level, maybe like a check,
like a check box, right?
So acquire third party SAS, right? Like,
so...
You know,
the role of the platform really for
non-core is to manage the integration and
to provide ease of integration because
this is where we make the money.
We want the feature kind of onboarding to
be very accessible, very fast.
We want the integration to be very clear,
very standard.
And so we can keep adding more and more
of this stuff over time without having to
build custom integrations every single
time because that's not cost effective,
right?
So the platform's job is,
in contrast to core products,
the platform job is to maintain the
hierarchy, right, and enforce it.
The platform's job for non-core is to
maintain the integration capabilities,
right,
and make it available so that anybody can
come to us and then we can decide,
you know,
like if we have a complicated system,
like a...
portfolio management system,
there's bits and pieces of it depending
on which PM system you use.
Do we care about how they fine-tune
feature and data access in there? No.
We just tell them this is the user.
Maybe we give them a little bit of
context of which firm because maybe they
run on a single tenant, right?
Here's the firm, here's the user.
here's the articles that this user have
access to, and then figure out the rest,
we don't care. PM system might say, well,
actually, no, no,
there's like trade non-trade still,
we want to know about that. Okay,
then the platform can pass you that as
well,
and then that would be a discussion with
the third party at the time of when we
onboard them and we do the integration.
Right. Other things we don't like,
we don't want to have that conversation,
like research.
It's all or nothing.
You get the research tool,
you get to look up research. That's it.
So there's no granularity of access.
It's called access research.
You have it or you don't, right?
I just make it one single assignable
feature as an add-on to any user in any
firm,
as long as the firm actually purchased
research from us.
So, when they when the firm come work,
then, for example,
let's say for research to research for
example,
and it's under our add-ons tab or
third-party app, whatever.
Then when the user comes to the Compass X
and click on Research Bloomberg,
here beforehand,
their SSO has been integrated into our
SSO or vice versa.
Vice person, the other way around,
because again, like, remember,
like the job for non-core or core, right,
to manage the product ecosystem is the
job of the platform.
The platform needs to be aware of which
firm and which user has what in any given
time, so it needs to come from us,
which means that we have all the context,
which means you need to give that firm
the context, which means they're all,
yeah, they have.
Yeah, from Firm 360, yeah, OK, yeah, well,
from Firm 360 down to, like,
so from the configuration down to the
platform implementation of the
configuration to platform configuration
within the platform to say,
do you have certain preferences like
white labeling?
I have that stored in Kung Fu,
and so any third party app that needs
that context, they need to ask us.
right, the platform to provide it.
They will never have that context if they
came into us.
And it's also a matter of entry points,
right? Like our users,
we want them to default to COPRESCOCHEF,
because that's where you get everything.
Why would I want you to log into a
research zone and then come through to us?
That flow doesn't make a lot of sense for
our current.
existing users because they're in our
ecosystem and they do things with us
anyway.
They use other tools in the system. Yeah,
that makes sense.
And who is in charge of that integration?
You are. I mean, with the third. OK.
That's part of platform manager. OK. Yeah.
OK.
That's why you need to go through
platform integrations.
Okay.
I mean, I mean, people joining Ali Azizi.
It's the whole. Oh, OK. You were OK. OK.
Sits under.
I just wanted to understand how internal
things are. Yeah,
that's why you have a dividing conquer.
Map here between you and Devindra is
you're here and then Devindra is here.
Ohh wow, yeah.
For now, like, I don't think it's for,
yeah, cleanly continents.
It's like whoever was had hands and can
do stuff. It's like,
I don't think that taking care of
integration or the platform UI changes
and is usually Paul. Yeah,
I know we gotta, we gotta re-divide it.
To make it more clean,
but David is working on notifications
here right now,
and we are doing the technical
integration or about the business
integration. We are the, it's the same,
it's us or it's coming from somewhere
else. What's the difference?
For example,
how we decide to approach Bloomberg.
It's we approach to Bloomberg or
Bloomberg comes to us, whatever. Oh,
I see. What's the front door or?
You mean from a like when do we decide or
something?
Well,
it's based on demand and where is the
main come from,
where we either push it or we hear about
it, or they come to us,
but because we don't have an open app
marketplace,
like vendors are not just going to show
up to our doors,
unless our clients are using that tool.
That's where it usually comes from.
Our clients are like, oh,
I don't want to have like 5 different
logins.
I just want to get it through confidence.
Why can't I have that?
That's really how it starts.
Okay, okay.
Or we see like, oh,
we're going out meeting clients and our
clients are not asking, but we see that,
you know,
20 clients are using the same technology
and we feel we can probably take over
that contract with better preferred
pricing than we started.
Did it ever happen?
That's how the P.M. tools came about,
Candi. They should in harmony.
OK, but then increases,
increases with the original, yeah.
We just have, yeah, we haven't just,
we just haven't done the SSR yet. Oh,
that's why digit and harling in that
package feature, which is, yeah,
don't have any features, yeah,
'cause it's like it doesn't exist, yeah,
okay, okay, all right,
shall we do we do we need?
I think I need a break.
Can we take a quick break and then we get
into the, I didn't even finish this part,
but I think I'll explain this as the last
piece,
because then that ties into again what
Graham needs to know about how feature
then gets presented to the user.
And the next session we'll get into based
on this, I think.
it would make sense to get into the
packaging. Yeah. Yeah.
On Thursday. On Thursday, yeah.
And then Graham, if you have time,
I think that would be a relevant one too.
Yes, please. Cool.
All right, can we take 5? No,
we can come back. Kevin,
we're gonna come back in five.
Sounds good.
Yeah, I'll clean it up,
but I'll explain it because it's a little
bit different.
You're not sharing it useful. Yep.
Yeah, I'm not checking so much.
I might wanna.
I might want to have another.
Supporting artifact. Give me one second.
The recording was on the whole time.
Muted. Muted. Did you guys mute the mic?
Did you? I've always been mute.
You get.
You guys are all muted.
Yeah, I was mute.
Were you trash talking to somebody that
shouldn't have been recorded?
You just did before you came in the room.
Yeah, well, I was on mute though. Okay,
good. Tell me you didn't hear anything,
did you?
Was it about me?
No, but I'll tell you. Well, I mean,
it was though, say it to his face. No.
Okay, then, no.
I heard nothing.
It was funny,
I was helping my in-laws book flights
yesterday and they're so technology inept
that they don't know how to mute.
So I was on the phone with them and it
was like a financial discussion and they
wanted to kind of sidebar.
And then the dad was whispering, I'm like,
Toby, like I heard everything.
Like you have a very loud whisper and
it's not proprietary information.
Like I needed to know this to help you
with the booking. It's just very funny.
It happens.
Hold on, give me one second. Awesome,
more crazy looking.
Okay.
So we'll get started again. I think,
let me see where we are with the agenda.
So we talked about, you know,
the platform,
the product ecosystem organization on in
the platform. Sure. Oh, ****, sorry.
I thought I was sharing something.
It says you are sharing. Yeah, you are.
Are you in the wrong meeting?
You didn't see it? Is it still recording?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I found it. Sorry.
All good.
All right,
so product ecosystem organization,
you know,
which is really about sort of like the
model and the lens we take to the core
and non-core features.
Once you get them registered and we'll
put the access and assignment,
all of that aside for the overview today
is, okay, you have it all in the system,
you have a discernment of core versus
non-core, you got a list of apps, okay,
how do we
Show it to users,
which again gets into a little bit.
I think this is more for like an FYI.
I'm not sure if it's fully relevant for
FBN UM,
maybe more relevant just as general
knowledge when it comes to feature
integration is we.
Because there is a breadth of features,
we're looking at 120 plus, I think,
right now on the platform.
You just can't list it and expect people
to find ****. That's not possible. Again,
that's how I think tools and apps was
born in R2.
is the more tools you build,
you run out of menu space or you shove it
in there.
You can invalidate this, by the way.
That was my interpretation when I first
saw the plaque. Scroll, scroll, scroll.
And then they take up, like,
so much real estate, right?
Like a description,
the laying of launch it, yeah, anyway, um,
so...
How do you sanely present this to clients?
Was part of the problem we had to solve
on what the platform needed to do, right,
is because you have 100 features,
more than 100 features,
we want to continue to expand that
feature set with value added services. So,
you know, optimistically,
hopefully in the future,
there would be more than.
100 features,
maybe there's like 200 features.
Like how do you get to a place where you
can grow and scale this in a way that
discoverability is still not an issue,
right? Feature discoverability,
like how do you know what you have?
And you can still be very efficient in
navigation of that,
especially in the core, like.
navigation is always problematic if you
have the wrong information architecture,
right? So it needs,
it actually needs a plan.
You can't just throw **** into a UI and
navigation and hope it works.
So,
and then maybe I'll maybe top that off to
say, you know,
we wanted to focus on this also because
we're supposed to be operations and
technology partners to these firms.
We're supposed to make their lives easier
if it's confusing to do business with us
and to do it their day-to-day
administration,
which occupies quite a lot of, you know,
like those the focus time who needs to
kind of going back up here,
who needs to do kind of all the jobs that
they're supposed to do.
If they're not doing it efficiently,
we're causing them, we're costing them,
right?
And so our ecosystem presentation needs
to still enable efficiency.
for the user at the end of the day.
The problem is, the problem is, again,
I go back to this,
is every good freaking bloody different
combinations of jobs, right? You know,
as an advisor,
my main orientation probably is in a
client or a household, right?
I want to really be focused on client
conversations and facilitating.
you know,
discussions with clients and all that
stuff.
My universe lives in client management.
I'm only managing the client.
I'm only helping them with investment
decisions, right?
I don't need to worry about regulatory
compliance. That's these people here.
I'm focused on selling and making money
and grabbing assets.
These people here needs to be able to
provide support for all the advisors.
Well, if you give me a navigation that,
sure, I can do account opening,
but I have to go into the account profile
to do all this stuff one by one. Like,
you imagine how efficient that gets over
time, right?
So we kind of said we got to organize our
features into workspaces that makes sense.
for these types of organizational setups,
end of the day, yes, you know,
all the specific nuances of how they
delegate their employees to do work might
be different at a user by user level,
but the jobs that they do and the job,
like the tasks that surround those jobs
are actually very similar.
So we said,
let's take a journey-led approach to
grouping features.
So, and you know, client journey, right?
So we kind of said, okay,
if you have a client servicing oriented
job, or if you are a head office, right,
and you're managing firm operations,
there is a cluster of features that you
need. If you're just managing clients,
there's a subset of cluster of features
that you need. By the way,
those features could be exactly the same,
which is different orientation.
Right?
Because if you're talking to a client
about, hey, got this great, you know,
like idea,
investment idea for you to meet your
objectives, whatever,
usually it's just selling products,
but we don't criticize your business
models. We're agnostic to that.
I just wouldn't go bank with them.
They might go, oh,
you should buy this fund. Right?
And the client's like, oh,
that's an amazing idea.
I'm going to buy this fund. Okay,
let's look up if you have enough money.
And if you don't have money,
let's go initiate a deposit of some money
from somewhere you can transfer it in.
I'm talking to you as an investor, Ali,
and I'm going to go pull up your account
profile for me to look all that stuff up.
And then if you have enough money, okay,
I'm still in your profile.
I'm just going to initiate the buy for
the fund that we just talked about.
I don't need to go anywhere else.
I'm in the account profile, right?
To kind of show you what that means,
let's actually log in for realsies and
take a look at it.
And so for advisors,
the only thing they really do is I'm in
accounts here, right?
And I'm gonna look up for. And I'm gonna,
I'm gonna kind of initiate a discussion
with you because,
and do we have a performance issue today?
Uh, because you're, um, oh,
that's training, that's the product.
Never remember that is 2Y101 product.
No, 201, because I'm talking to you,
Mister Product Team,
and Mister Product Team,
you want to buy some stuff.
And so I'm just going to see,
have you bought something most recently?
Are you sure you want to do this again?
Right? Oh, looks like you have,
but not recently. Okay.
And then I'm going to talk to you about
your positions. Oh, you hold nothing.
Maybe you want to hold something.
I see that. Oh, ****,
you don't have enough cash to buy
anything.
So I want to be here right here and then
initiate some transfer.
in of money so we can purchase that fund
you say you wanted to do, but if you,
let's say you have money,
because we can't actually do this for
this account,
maybe I want to go into here and look at
initiating that fund purchase that we
talked about. And right here,
I've got all the information I need.
I'm going to come into here and then I'm
just going to buy that ****** cash.
product that I talked to you about, right?
And I'm going to place the order right
here then. This is actually orders.
It's not accounts. Yeah.
This is the orders feature, right?
But the way I bring it together,
we want to make sure that it's still,
it's relevant for the kind of like the
key personas that we have so that.
They're very efficient. I can go here,
here, here. I'm not going anywhere.
I'm actually just kind of still on the
same screen,
being able to access all the spokes of
actions that I have.
We call them the hub and spoke model.
The hub is accounts.
The spokes are all the actions that hang
off of it. Oh, yeah.
Not hub and spoke from a microservices
architecture perspective.
That's different.
This is UI hub and spoke.
But.
Okay, so that's kind of like,
that's kind of the game plan.
And if I'm not the advisor,
because you know,
I am now the person or Graham is now the
operations person and I'm an advisor and
I'm super busy and I'm trying to deal
with you and oh ****,
you need to move money. I'm going to say,
Graham is going to help me with that.
You're going to file it away,
you're going to follow up and make sure
that the money gets in,
especially if it's like a transfer
because it's like a multi-kind of day
thing.
Graham is not going to do this for all
our clients in the company because we
have like a million accounts.
So I'm going to actually not do that.
not place a trade in the product team
account. And I'm going to,
let's say it's orders because we only
have that,
we don't have transfers in here.
I need to monitor orders for everybody,
right? So I'm going to go here instead.
And this gives me a view,
a cross-account view,
cross-sectional view of just orders.
Remember that specialization we talked
about earlier?
Right?
So I'm going to have a universe where I'm
going to help a firm at the head office
level do their operations,
but I'm also going to support,
which is one key persona, right?
Because you need to run your business and
you need to do all of this administration
across all of your accounts.
But I'm also going to have a view,
I'm going to have another hover of people
that just need to live in the context.
Of a client or an account,
which is right now, it's here,
but it's gonna look a little bit
different in the target navigation,
and then here would be basically a subset
of all of this stuff that I can do in
context of the account itself, right?
So I can do, I can do the same thing.
I can, I can initiate an order here,
but knowing that I can do it for anybody,
well, I'm gonna have to,
I'm gonna have to look up that account.
Right. Yeah. Which it finally works.
It's sorted in the right order.
This is wonderful. Although,
what is the name is the name different?
OK, we'll do that later.
This is prod, so it shouldn't happen.
OK, so right, so quick demo of that,
which means, sorry,
I have seen something in some banks,
for example, CDC. Yeah,
one day I go to branch or even for the
phone.
When they want to get access to my
account, they pass me one OTP. Yeah.
And then I read to them.
Is it something that takes place here or
it's an operation of the KYC that takes
place inside?
For example, Industrial Alliance. OK,
because we we we're in the B2B
relationship,
like the B2C part is what our firms do,
so that is we expect that to come from
them, but how it's integrate,
maybe they don't have this.
because before this KYC,
they should have this privilege to access
these accounts. Correct. So, so anyway,
without the OTP, they already have this.
Well, because the access to the, like,
so the OTP, the purpose of that though,
right, is.
is not to gain access to your profile.
That's not all the reps have access to
your all your accounts.
If you're a TD customer,
they have access to it.
It's to verify you. Are you Ali for sure?
I don't want you pretending to be Ali.
That's the verification.
I was thinking the other way. Yeah, yeah,
right. Yeah, exactly. No,
because if you're an employee, like,
you actually just call client services.
right, of that firm.
That client services comes into here.
Okay, you know, Ali or Mr. Product Team,
right?
We're going to discuss and see what you
want to do, but first,
I'm going to verify some details.
Can you tell me, right,
what your occupation is,
what we masked that and we masked that,
so that's not a verification, right?
Can you give me some details around where
you live? Right? Yeah. And your e-mail,
which is Ray Norris, CA.
And then tell me if, like,
so that's the verification in that, like,
yeah,
they use this platform or their own
platform to pull your client profile,
right? And then, once you're done again,
I'm here now. OK, good. You're for sure,
Mister Product Team.
What can I do for you today,
Mister Product Team? Ohh, well, you wanna.
..
transfer some money or you want to look
up some stuff,
you want to pull up your latest statement,
okay, I can do that for you.
And in terms of the transfer, for example,
do we have integration with InTrack or...
That's a rabbit hole you don't want to
get into. No,
I just as a general question. Yeah,
payments, again, all of this.
Stuff is managed by the app that actually
facilitates the either the money movement
or the transfers, yeah,
the different systems,
how they're actually facilitated,
whether it's real-time or not. I mean,
none of our stuff is mostly real-time
anyway.
It's we let the bank deal with all the,
ohh, okay, yeah.
Remember,
where the distributor of that experience,
right? So we just take the app,
we just trust that the app,
you got the right plumbing.
Sometimes we don't like the plumbing
because it's not real time, go fix it,
right?
Real time payments is coming up now,
go do the integration with real time
payments so that we can do same day money
movement.
But we and BNI doesn't manage that
because we don't run the app.
But, for example,
having enough funds to invest,
so being if...
For example, over the phone, say, okay,
I have transferred $10,000. Okay,
how we can see that, you know,
there should be a background. Yeah, yeah,
that goes back to, remember,
the book of record facilitates all of
that,
all these apps really punch in requests
and transaction requests into the book of
record.
Book of record may imply some validations
on top of what we do,
and then that thing hooks up to all the
payment rails, like whether it's Swift,
not interact, because that's peer-to-peer,
right?
Like it hooks up to whether it's the
transfer rail or the payment rail or the
exchange, right, in case of trading.
We don't care about that,
it deals with that. Okay, that's fine.
And then obviously because of this
integration, when it comes back,
what is our app do? Well, it views, right?
So we just pull the data back from the
book of record to show it. Good.
Thank you.
Total sidebar.
So if that's the client,
how was it in the orders that it was like
a... Oh, you have to go into an account.
Because you can only transact at the
account level, right? For some stuff? Yes,
but when you did the order,
like when you tried to do an order at the
account level, why did it show capital N,
lower BNI? Is it like, are the... Oh,
I see what you mean.
Like the names coming from the account?
Cut, or do they not?
This is actually,
this is the account name. I,
so there's some fluckery with the
accounts API. Okay. Like, so you see here,
that's the account name,
but then we show a different name here.
This is a Kevin problem. But in the past,
because the order modules was built first
before the accounts module.
They used a different representation of
accounts. The search was different.
They just like they like all the data is
the same in the background,
but they just decided to pull from a
different attribute, I believe,
is what happened.
Okay.
I don't like what I'm seeing right now.
No, of course not. This is crazy.
I don't know who did that.
I think they,
I think they put the client name in here
and then I think they didn't do something
about this. Like,
I don't know why this happened.
Adam.
So those attributes still exist?
Somewhere, yeah,
in our accounts database somewhere.
But,
but it shouldn't be presented as the O.K.?
No, this is a bug. K. Kevin.
Wait,
let me take a screenshot of that before
It's going to take this. Yeah, OK.
you go.
Oh, good, good testing.
Yeah, we don't know why,
but for sure the accounts module was
using a different account search because
like these things here are supposed to be
common components.
Right, so like, well,
this thing is a read,
but then if you go into the master order
ticket,
this should be the same account search as
when you do the search account here. Yeah.
Right,
which I'm pretty sure is not the same.
Like if I did this, no counts count.
Maybe, yeah,
so it's definitely a different search.
Doesn't even show the name.
Sir, I didn't mean to... No, no, no.
It's A long-standing issue.
I suspect Avindra knows about it.
We just never got around to fixing it.
because our IT team were not talking to
each other at the time.
And so they decided to build a custom
version for this versus the order search
versus the search at this level.
And we told them, you guys are idiots,
it's the same search.
So we won't get into the common component
discussion. That's a, it's a bag of fun,
but this is why.
We want to externalize the design system
and we want to externalize component
libraries for infinite.
Because imagine creating the 4th, the 5th,
the 6th version of this, right? Yeah,
yeah.
a bit painful and it's been built already.
So Owen is in the process. Well,
I say in the process,
I've been trying because we're waiting
for the UI designer to come on,
to come on board. Now that he's on board,
Owen does need to do a knowledge transfer
at minimum on the design system,
so the behaviors are the same.
And ideally,
we find a way to externalize those common
UI components.
So we don't have to keep building the
same thing over and over again.
It's like a waste of code.
Like it's a waste of time.
Yeah, same thing with this,
like you'll see the consistency is
supposed to be there for this module list,
right? This is a module,
it's the accounts module,
and the filtering,
there's supposed to be layout,
the sorting,
should be the same as what's here, right?
Placed a little bit differently,
but it's because it's actually the same
components.
over and over again.
That's this is why this is how we do away
without having to do bespoke design on
everything. Once you have a design system,
you have a standard,
you don't need to do design anymore.
You don't need a designer. And Kevin,
this is why we do a consistency
discussion, even for file upload is.
They should be reusing stuff so that we
don't have to write custom code for it
every single time. And by the way,
beauty of this is if one day,
because it was on the roadmap for a long
time,
we decide to provide the ability for a
client to customize their layout that was
in the prototype, I add a custom layout.
subcomponent to the module list component,
it appears everywhere.
It works for every single module that
uses that module list.
Right, and if I have 10 modules,
you don't have to update it 10 times,
right? It just takes the metadata and,
you know,
saves it to the per to the person's
profile.
Okay, that was a side question. Sorry.
I have one question. Yeah.
I see that the account management and
trading right now exists here. Yeah. Yeah.
Netrip is also for trading, is that right?
It is, yes.
This is pre-beta. Nobody has this.
Only me and Stan and a handful of people
have it. Oh, yeah.
Is how is this related to NetRep?
It's a view of the NetRep or is this
totally another? Good question.
So remember, going back to Book of Record,
NetRep is a...
proprietary app for trading that's bolted
onto the book of record provided by
Broadridge. It's A Broadridge product.
So NetRep sits,
has a proprietary direct integration with
the book of record for trading.
That's why we need a separate login,
it's a separate app.
The things that you punch in goes
directly into the book of record in
NetRep. So if you buy,
sell securities in NetRep, it goes in.
Same thing goes into the book of record,
right?
And so that's a standalone thing that
lives outside of Compass.
It just has existed since the dawn of
time. What we said we were going to do is,
well,
that doesn't make any sense over there
because you can't access through here and
there's a whole bunch of specific
training product limitations with NetRep.
Right, including the, you know,
some of the file pulls that we talked
about before.
You can't build that into NetRip.
It's A proprietary app.
You can't change it. It's super old.
Like I think it's like 20 years old or
something. It's crazy old, right?
So we need to get rid of that if we want
to evolve our trading product offering.
We built it from scratch.
We built it from scratch in here. Okay.
And so this version is actually does
identical to what NetRep does.
It's just a new app that's hosted in the
platform, plus more things that we added.
And obviously you can see we can do quite
a lot more to it.
But it also does the job of talking
directly to the book of record for orders.
Yeah, for sure. So if you place in that,
if you actually place an order today on
NetRep, like I can see it here,
half of these orders are placed on NetRep.
and then vice versa, right? So that,
you know,
we're talking from the same source,
like to your point, like 2 sessions ago,
you know,
we're not making **** up on the
integration channels, it's the same.
And then that's how we actually
transition people off because not
everybody be,
not everybody can move at the same time
with our clients.
And then some might want to, they, hey,
I want to try out this new trading
solution,
but all my advisors or all my portfolio
managers are still a net rep.
I need to have that interoperability
through the transitionary period.
Because remember,
they have to do their trade recons at a
minimum every day,
where are they recalling that from?
So the.
They need to have to view the accounts
and orders in both places, yeah,
and then all the order consistency,
like I don't want to test it because then
I'll need to ask somebody to cancel it,
but you technically place an order in net
rep, it'll show up here,
you place an order here,
it will show up in net rep,
but ultimately it's all in the record,
yeah. Thank you.
Good, good, good question.
This is a pre-release module.
It's here because we need to test it
before it goes out. Okay. Thanks.
Okay.
Back to here, I I don't think there's too,
like I don't think we need to get too
deep into this.
It's more for awareness is so when we
ultimately, you know,
our organization of the navigation comes
down to the this workspace concept so
that we use kind of this kind of like.
The formal kind of UXUI terminology is a
hub and spoke model,
but we call it workspaces.
It's just a little bit easier to
understand.
There's 2 things that allow us to have
that fluidity in what we just saw.
One is the workspace organization,
so grouping of features into the right
kind of space so that all the related
features kind of sit together and in.
When you're in there,
you can kind of navigate around and it
makes sense to you.
We really only have two hubs.
It's the firm or the client at this stage.
But we can get it.
There's like another picture where I can
get into it in more granularity.
And then the other thing that the
platform enforces, well,
it's more of a the platform physically
doesn't implement anything.
We're saying that.
a standard of way of building
applications on top of all these other
standards we just talked about is
allowing for modularity, right?
So if we didn't build orders the way we
did, so let's go back into here.
Orders is a module in its own right,
but we also register actions.
This is a modal,
but it's also a micro app.
If we build our actions in a way that I
can take certain pieces of it and put it
somewhere else,
that's how you create the fluidity.
Because I know that, like I said,
there's at least two different entry
points depending on your personal and
minimum for just for orders,
like not even anything else, right?
I'm either in context of the account that
you just saw because I'm talking to a
client, or I'm in context of clients,
like, you know,
a trade support team or somebody who's
supporting all this inflow of trades and
I need to help kind of execute some of
the orders.
I have a cross account or cross firm view
of my universe.
I'm not going to go into the account
profile and then switch to the next
account profile and switch to the next
account profile to do all this trades,
right?
So at minimum, we call that, well,
there's two entry points.
There's 2 even UI entry points for that
task.
I have to be able to facilitate both of
those or even more, right?
The entry point could be,
we talked about Industrial Alliance,
AX 360, their own advisor platform.
They might want to initiate trade from
there. Actually,
it makes the most sense because they want
to keep advisor in context of what the
advisor's day-to-day is,
which is in AX 360.
Right?
So if we don't have a bit of a game plan,
especially for the core stuff,
to be able to take that stuff feature and
allow the integration and all the
presentation of it into wherever user,
like wherever the user flow kind of comes
in from to access that action,
we're not making it efficient for them,
right? Imagine I'm kind of, again,
I'm having the same conversation.
in industrial lines now. Right,
let's play the cell in like painful
detail. I'm gonna go, again,
I'm gonna do the same thing. Guess what?
They do this search to pull up the client
profile.
in AX 360, not Compass.
So all of this stuff is in another system
that the firm owns that they've built.
And well,
what if I need to initiate a transaction
from there? I have to come into Compass,
do that same search and pull up that
profile.
Or we can say Industrial Alliance.
We have a very flexible integration of
votes that allows you to integrate by a
back end or even the front end in
addition to SSO if you want to pull in a
transaction, we can do that.
That's what we want.
We can't do that right now.
That's where we want to be.
So that I'm in AX 360 and I need to move
money because.
You know, I'm in, right? I'm in,
I'm in debit. I'm gonna pull up a EFT,
right? Right in AX360. It's our EFT form,
but they can pull it up. Yeah.
If they're not in debit,
they want to trade, I'm gonna pull in,
they're gonna call the same thing, right?
We're not gonna build like another whole
different thing and they're not gonna
build an order ticket. Like this is,
this is our solution, right?
So they're gonna take this micro app.
And we're going to be able to say,
you can call this micro app in your front
end, right?
And the background obviously would
facilitate the SSOs, you can get to it,
and then you just need to get access to
that feature, right?
And then they can present it in AS 360.
And so how we facilitate like a really
seamless,
efficient user experience is to design
stuff that's modular enough that I can.
Put it in different places and support
the integration to those things, right?
So the integration pattern actually for
this ticket is actually exactly the same
as if X360 calls this thing,
because it's actually calling the SSO,
authorizing access to this feature,
and then presenting this feature back up
as an app.
Everything we built in Compass X is API
driven, API enabled, correct,
and my graph enabled. OK,
so when I say API enabled, it means that..
.
There is an authentication and
authorization level on top of that. Yes.
For example,
IA can integrate orders module with
invoking those APIs and pass through that
authentication and authorization.
which that authorization and
authentication sits inside our, yeah.
Yeah.
Small adjustment to that thought process
is we don't facilitate direct API off
today. And so when you access,
like when you do like experience
integration and you want to access that
micro app.
The, it's the micro app.
Like you still have the API authorization,
but it's at the app level per user.
It's not a system to system authorization.
We don't have that yet.
I didn't understand.
Maybe Candi can make studies better.
Oh, this part, you know,
I didn't understand in context of what we
have going through. You know,
I technically I don't understand,
but this distinction. Okay,
we can get into it more.
So like there is a distinction to say.
If I want to call this URL or this micro
app URL, I don't have it, is. Well,
I think technically we have to, yeah,
the SSO, how it works.
You have to come through the SSO. Yeah,
yeah, the SSO,
I think you're talking about the API
integration.
Someone just build some things,
building on the website and then click on
it and trying to place an order.
But we're not facilitating,
we're on the track of doing that.
We have a API marketplace initiative.
We're offering some API for external
firms.
That's the race teams work on that
offering.
But not everything's exposed to external
call yet. So I think for now, accounts,
accounts API is open to external call.
So if you want to integrate something,
maybe pull back your position or some
other things from your account history.
that you can call the endpoints from your
portal, from your sites.
But that one goes through system token
and there's a whole lot of different
authorization you have to do and
authentication. So that's not.
So, what the platform team we here handle,
so those for, yeah, OK, yeah, raise team,
and then here, if the, let's say, IBM,
how the single sign work is,
they provide one link only,
and that link would open up.
the campus portal.
So they lend the client onto portal with
a single sign on authentication and that
depends on what the user has access to,
it will render the site for them.
So that's what we call the single sign is
on the platform level.
Okay, okay.
Right,
so it's a fragmented user experience in
terms of the API and what we have in
Compass, because Compass X,
because in the API that the other team
offers to, for example,
to Industrial Alliance.
There are limited packages, for example,
only probably on orders and trade package.
Yeah.
And I guess it's not that granular as we
are in our feature registry. Correct.
Whole package. Yeah. And then.
It's up to the industrial alliance how to
grant permissions to internal users on
their own platform. Yeah. Okay. Yeah,
that's right. So it's a different,
different flow, but ultimately, if, if,
if,
if we were to reuse the APIs that we've
built for Compass,
because some of them are just not.
Built for externalization,
they're not fit for purpose,
but if we take an instance of it,
then technically your entry point for the
API marketplace is the API authorization
right to those same APIs,
and the authorization would be done very
similarly with a very similar mechanism,
because you don't want to create
different platforms,
but different endpoints,
but different endpoints, and also...
like who authorizes is different.
So here you get SSO access into a compass,
right,
or you get access to access into an app.
The app handles the authorization with
the APIs because they go together,
but the app talks to the APIs because the
apps like the API is part of the app,
right? And so we don't need.
Extra authorization for that, it's a ohh,
your compass, yeah, you're good, right?
Because we already dealt with the feature
access,
we already dealt with the data access,
you know, we're supposed to have this,
you know, it says the user,
like the what the user is authorized to
this,
like scopes are included in that
authorization, and so.
It's a our API doesn't have to discern
where the request is coming from.
It's always coming from COPRESCOCHEF.
If we were to externalize and this is the
missing externalization step,
now I need to recognize what system it's
coming from or firm it's coming from,
right?
And no longer just which user is coming
from to get that context.
Our APIs can't do that right now. Yeah.
OK, but it's the same API,
so it could be the same APIs. Yeah, yeah,
makes sense.
And yes,
the granularity is different as well,
because, you know,
these are users at the end of the day who
have jobs.
When it comes to API integration,
it's system to system, right?
So the system requirement is probably
more at the capability level.
unless we want to sell them individually,
which some of them we do.
How do we get into this modularity?
That's how we got into this.
So Graham's nodding his head,
but don't approve violently because not
everything's built this way.
We only started with orders.
I wish for everything to be built this
way, but it's not.
So when we get to the transfers
management,
we're going to have the same discussions.
Like, how do you do this with infinite?
Infinite is not doing this.
Everything's bespoke.
Very consent.
Start baby steps. Start with the,
and so while that's kind of like the
model, usually,
as you can see with firm user management,
we do this with everything else.
We cut corners like no tomorrow for our
time to market.
And so we're getting really good at
building the firm, like, so this is.
basically the firm hub.
We're getting really good at building
firm level stuff.
So accounts work at the firm level.
You see if I go into here,
I can see the list of all.
These are workspaces on the left side.
This is actually the workspace.
Like this thing is the firm workspace.
When I get into the context of accounts,
then this is the accounts workspace.
So we only have two. Okay, yeah. Yeah,
for now, there might be more,
but more would just come from how many
other types of products are we going to
distribute. This is our aspirations,
is what are the different workspaces?
Well, we know that.
firms run their operations with literally
an operations team.
Part of the operation is investment
operations, which is us, right?
This is the oldest, all our core services,
makes up a subset of a firm needs to do.
But if you're a company, well,
you got to do company things.
It's not just investment operations.
It's a big part of it, but.
other things like accounting, billing,
fees, you know, reporting,
managing business performance.
Like if you run a business,
you got to do all that stuff too.
You need tools for all that other stuff.
So that stuff also lives in what we call
the firm, the firm kind of hub,
firm space. You'll see as you.
grow the product lines,
actually NBI can offer some of these
tools for firms.
And so we kind of group that all to say,
okay,
if you're coming in and you're managing
the firm operations,
you're going to need a holistic set of
firm tools,
and that's your firm workspace.
We only provide this slice today,
but there's going to be more reporting.
There's going to be analytics.
There's going to be us helping you with
some of that business performance.
There's going to be us helping you with
some of the
firm follow-ups day-to-day,
so you stay on top of your administration.
There might be even tools for us to help
you, you know, do billing,
which kind of relates to this,
but it's coming, right?
And so I need to create a firm ecosystem,
so when you land here,
all the stuff I see that's relevant to
manage my firm operations shows up in
this primary workspace that I have.
Right. However, if, like I said,
if I'm not advisor and like I said,
the PM advisor persona is similar,
they're client facing,
they're front office, I'm going to manage,
you know,
client relationships or household
relationships.
I'm really operating up here.
I don't care about any of this stuff.
And advisors aren't going to deal with
billing. Right.
And they're not going to like.
Sort of, you know, pay invoices. They,
they, they live up here,
so why do I show them everything?
I just need to show them a subset and
some stuff that's specifically related
for the advisor experience or the PM
experience, and we call that the,
you know, the admin hub,
where the admin workspace.
We're here to help you manage to give you
a...
subset of a collection of features that
only makes sense to you.
I'm not going to distract you with
anything else.
I want to prove that you were the firm
desktop, an advisor desktop experience.
We have some stuff emerging here actually.
We're cooking up some stuff.
And I say we don't do the SSO this way
around, but we might do in the future,
I don't know, is we have non-retail.
offerings. So institutional, true B2B,
there's no C at the end. B2B offerings.
And some of that stuff might not even be,
you know,
people who have firm structures in their
accounts as a book of record.
We have side businesses that don't go
into the book of record.
I'm not going to go into it,
but we call them our institutional.
arms of the business. Well,
they have tools too that's completely
different to what's here.
So why am I giving them all this ****
when I just need to give them the
institutional tools?
So we have an institutional hub concept,
which has like, you know,
like more advanced research tools
potentially,
like more securities kind of like
financial data tools,
like a bunch of stuff goes into there.
Even kind of like stuff that our prime
broker desk do,
technically that's a B2B relationship.
So there's some **** that goes on there.
And a fund administration tools go into
here as well, fund administration.
If you're a fund manager, well,
you need to do fund administration,
accounting, taxes and all that ****.
We have a team that has outsourced that
to S triple G, that services our firms,
that's B2B, that goes into here,
doesn't have anything to do with managing
clients and accounts.
So it's not in the platform today,
but we might have a hub that do that as
well. And then ultimately, tail end of it,
we actually have an investor portal. We,
it's a ******* child,
we put it to the side.
Kevin's going to fix a strategy for it,
so I'm not going to get into it right now.
But ideally,
that's another variation of COPRESCOCHEF.
You're Ali the investor, you talk to me,
I'm the firm, firm banks with NBIN,
it's all the same ****, right?
So today I have a tool that allows you to
log in to see your profile,
just like online banking.
But it is a completely different app
that's built by another team in the bank
that still kind of talks through the book
of record, but not in the way we do.
So, it's a little inconsistent,
and why this should in...
It's inside COPRESCOCHEF.
It doesn't today. It's completely outside.
Yeah, it should. I was. But it's,
it comes down to a question of the way we
stack this up like this, right,
is because we are actually reusing all of
the features.
as we move up the chain. Oh, okay. Right.
And the thing that we don't reuse is
building a account view.
Right, for somebody here,
like this is a real person,
they're going to log into my portfolio
plus, which is our investor app,
and they're going to see a list of their
accounts and they're going to see their
profile documents.
They're going to see all this stuff,
but it's just built completely,
like as a complete separate standalone
app.
Can you potentially reuse some of these
modules that we have in COPRESCOCHEF?
That's for Kevin to the side.
Or we might acquire like yet another
third party app that makes it everything
look nicer and prettier because it's more
accessible in that case.
But that that's a that's that's we call
that we consider that a completely
separate workspace.
So the big picture gotta be here. Yeah,
don't worry about the no, that's good.
Don't worry about that standard Ward,
but like this is how, like,
if like we have kind of this that kind of
this UXUI concept, right?
The information architecture,
a well structured then.
technically you can infinitely expand
these hubs based on what people do, right?
And you might even kind of carve out
while firm operations becomes a
specialization,
investment operations becomes a
specialization of hubs.
You experience this today,
you look at if you use any other SAS
platforms.
Right, like, even if you're in like Azure,
right? Like, yeah,
you got these workspaces,
it's because there's some thinking behind
how to distribute the features, exactly,
in a in a in a consolidated way,
so this is really what we have today.
I'll end it here.
Because this is a lot of talking.
So, well,
not what we have today is kind of what we
envision today. And the beauty of this,
because we're still in the investment
kind of universe,
we're still in the core services universe
is, and this is all I want to have,
because we don't actually have too much
of this other stuff,
the firm desktop versus the admin.
But at the core of both,
there is an intersection,
which is everybody needs to see clients
and everybody needs to manage your
portfolio.
So we know that if we built these things
the right way, it can go,
we can put it into the firm desktop,
just like you saw,
and we can also stuff it into the admin
desktop, just like you saw there.
And then within portfolios where there's
a suite of capabilities, right, in client
There's a suite of capabilities and then
we have,
I guess we have some of this stuff which
is not in this picture.
That's why I want to pull up the other
one. Hold on.
I want to show your our coverage today.
Looks a little crazy.
is the last of is all the tools we have
and how the features map into the
workspaces.
Hold on, I'm not sharing the right screen.
Kevin, sorry, Kevin,
can you see the PowerPoint or Graham?
You're nodding. Okay, good. Great.
So superimposing what we have,
Yep, yep.
this kind of explains a little bit why
our UI is organized in a certain way.
Yeah. Great. We got,
you got kind of client tools,
you've got portfolio tools.
All of this has two different views.
One is a client-centric view in the admin
desktop,
but then we also give a flat list at the
top level for firm desktop.
We really only truly support the
operations functions for anybody who
needs to run firm operations with a
little bit of like kind of compliance
support. We provide reporting and data.
for some of the control functions.
But for operations,
the operations really is applicable to
any administration activities,
which is our core services against
clients or their portfolios.
That's what this is.
So you don't need to know this, know this,
because this is very context specific to
our product lines.
But just to explain that when, okay,
when we do onboard then.
a new feature,
we also indicate what hub that feature
lives in. And when we indicate the hub,
then we say, okay, if you're else,
if you need to put something in the admin
hub or the client hub,
now you need to give us a micro app
version of that.
And so we can stuff it in there in
context of the client hub actions.
So transfer would be in the next
conversation because transfers management
is already built.
It's kind of sitting over there somewhere.
It fits into this universe because you
can go in and you can see a consolidated
view of the operations of clients as it
relates to account servicing.
You can see that,
but it doesn't appear here because this,
you need to put transfers in context of
the accounts and we haven't created that.
kind of sub, I guess,
sub view that fits into the admin hub yet.
So you're gonna just see it here. Ideally,
every time we onboard something, if it,
if there's an intersection,
it goes to both places.
If there isn't like finance, like,
you know, your billing functions,
this doesn't have any connectivity to the
admin desktop.
So you're not gonna try to shove a
finance function into the admin desktop.
This graph has elasticity,
I mean to move these objects or add more.
Uh, you know, leg to the tree. Yeah,
more hubs, yeah, more spokes to the hubs,
yeah, hope, yeah.
In reality, it's actually,
I don't know if I should show this or not,
the original,
the origination of idea of that
intersection really comes from,
you build a set of features and then you
can kind of roll it up to,
like you can kind of roll all this stuff
into the firm desktop.
I think before when we started the old
compass,
it was a lot of the focus was here.
We don't have a lot of firm level stuff
in old compass.
So it's not acknowledging that need or
like we build it inconsistently, I guess.
Some stuff have the firm versus the
accounts level and some stuff don't.
I see reporting inside a couple of times,
but I don't see any trail inside Compass
X. Sorry? I see, for example,
data reporting in other areas,
but I haven't seen any footprint inside
Compass X where they sit in Compass X.
They're not,
they're not incorporated into Compass X
yet, so we have a few somewhere else.
Well, one of them is a secured zone tool,
so you know when that's coming. OK,
two of them,
actually two of them firm reporting and
CR. You'll see the word CRMA,
the credit risk monitoring.
That's these two here for.
compliance and oversight,
you'll see them in Q4 because you're
bringing them in, right?
Data exports already there,
that's the other tool. Yeah,
and then others are in development,
like the more analytic stuff is still
being cooked up by Ray's data team,
by Darwin and Babita.
So it means that if I want to see the
performance of my portfolio,
I don't come to Compass X.
I have a new another URL.
I and today enter my credential and see
my portfolio performance with charts,
granular.
tables, all sorts of things. Well,
I guess you have to ask yourself,
what is that map to here?
And what do our firms do today?
Like where do they get that from?
We're A custodian member.
We make sure we're the record keeper.
Yeah. We don't deal with investments.
So firms, you manage.
the performance of the portfolio that you
create for your clients,
we don't want to touch that. Okay. Right.
And so will we ever have an encompass?
Well, if we help them with that tooling,
sure. Which I, by the way,
is what a portfolio management system
typically does,
is it presents you with a view of
performance.
right,
of your portfolio so you can make
decisions based on performance and other
metrics that you have.
That's a very sophisticated piece of tool,
right?
So we're not going to ever build it,
we're going to acquire it and our firms
all actually have a PM system today and
that's where they go.
OK, we can, yeah,
we can come back to revisit that, yeah,
maybe, maybe,
maybe we can get Wilson to show you what
a PM system looks like, yeah.
Okay.
And that was it. So this, there's,
you know,
I don't feel like the main take away is
there's just,
there's this method to madness when it
comes to feature integration. No,
that makes sense.
It's categorized rationally and we can't.
We can witness the would bring up how the
package feature registry comes from, yeah,
yeah, that makes sense, yeah.
But that's why sometimes there would be,
when you look at the product hierarchy,
the product hierarchy should be pretty
intact.
It helps you kind of figure out which
features belong together, right?
Because they're all related tasks that
people do.
But then where it lands in the navigation
is an extra level of interpretation on
top of where do I implement this
hierarchy and how many places do I put
this?
group of features into. That's where Owen.
That's where Owen comes in.
That's where the information architecture
comes in.
And that's where sometimes there's
actually differences on how we define the
packaging versus how we group things in
the UI.
But they don't have to be the same.
We're just trying to make the experience
more efficient.
Long story short.
I think we're going to end it here for
today. Yeah, thank you. Yeah, great.
Alright,
stop this recording so we don't record
chit-chat.